Hello, oh
Okay, say it wants to poke the bear, but I believe ready bad buddy bloody blah, okay, that's fine. We can do that
Yeah, I was like done talking about you
You're being disgusting. Why are you bringing up people's kids?
Like honestly, why are you bringing up people's kids? You ding dong. You still you're you're talking about me and still only getting 21 viewers
That's pretty insane, dude
Let's fast forward let's rewind
Let's see where did I see that what part of that was it hold on
Hold on
Um
Where he's talking about me again
Let's see what time that was hold on hey pack yourself up. Okay. I'm trying to find the part
Time frame
Wait, I think I just found it
Yeah, okay
So he's taking an old photo from 2020 which was six years ago. Yes. I know I used a I all my
Freakin photo on the YouTube because of people like you Zaya
Brrr
Burn. Okay, since you want to obsess about me after I literally said who the fucking problem is and the fact that you want to defend
Brandon Q
You're threatening to protest in front of my house
My neighbor's a cop
Okay, if I'm a fucked up nigga, so is fucking brain. It brings a fucked up nigga. So is fucking gamble
He gambles a fucked up nigga. So is cock-eye mayors
i'm dead what the fuck did you not see the brain and click i'm so dead
oh my goodness dude leave me alone i don't even know you
You're weird as fuck. Why don't you grow facial here on your face? Why is it just your neck? It's kind of hard
Okay, you're crying like a little fucking bitch nigga when the game mentality comes your way and all of a sudden I gotta feel bad
No, bitch. No bitch. Like you said, nigga
Why are you filming the death of Athena? Like what is wrong with this guy?
What he is crazy
What?
You want to throw this in front of my house?
And for what?
I live next to my cop.
What the fuck?
Oh my god.
Wait a minute, everybody.
Is anybody going to buy your shoe?
You listen to people that I don't.
They're fucking bloodhurt.
from the fucking monkey ass
K-bigger to that fucking faggot ass demon bullmonger
Well, it's on his stream. He's still live, but I'm rewound it. I was like, oh, this guy wants to talk about me now
He's right on the same IQ level as Brandon Alex inside. I didn't even know yeah
Outside my house or your house. I'm not sure which house. He's the fucking reason he ain't protesting around anyone's house
He doesn't know where I live ain't nobody's
Somebody gonna buy a shoe collection behind him
I don't know. I don't think, you know, Cardi may not be DX anymore, but I don't think she's going to pay for him to vote against.
I mean, no, why would Cardi, he'd be homeless if he does tries to do that to one of us.
But Crystal, I had something funny. I didn't know he was live and doing this. I didn't mean to like derail.
But there's just one thing I wanted to show people because I think that it would make you and everybody smile.
Real quick. Yeah, I only by the way, I got the hyah from that person and if I knew how to sit it to you
I would but I can't but yeah. Oh, I told you I told did I not tell you I know ambers like hugs and kisses
No, that person that's been peeping all these penal bars and they've been all accusing each other has been because of
Oh, okay. Well here, hold on, Crystal. Look at my screen. Let me know if you guys can see. Crystal may not be able to hear now that I'm showing the screen.
Hello?
I don't know. You see? See?
I can hear.
Crystal? Okay, she can. All right. Put this up. Put the thing up. Let's see if you guys can hear this. Everybody, here you go. This is who we're dealing with.
That is all I feel like saying today. Fuck it, fuck it. Because I don't give a fuck if that.
Fuck it fuck it as I roll down the street and Cali, no one can fuck with me. Fuck it fuck it
That's pebs
Fuck it fuck it
Did she say Beckett?
Shit
I just fell
Oh my god
I'm okay.
Oh my god.
Who is that?
What do you think it is, Crystal?
I'm okay.
Alex. Alex Myers.
Fuck.
You've got it.
Oh my god.
Fuck it.
Woo!
Shit.
Oh my god
Like these are the successful people that everybody needs to be afraid of
This chick and then the bald pedophile and then the other pedophile
Vita really loves that BBC.
Vita's got a secret.
Oh my god.
Everybody knows.
He's in the dungeon.
Wherever he goes.
He wants to eliminate himself.
Put it out when he's around.
She can't help but shout out.
Vita loves that BBC.
I've seen this one before.
She wants it.
She and me want this.
I never saw any of this shit.
Oh, shoot.
I hadn't seen any of this shit, guys.
Please.
It's catchy as hell, not gonna lie.
Uh-oh.
But I mean wait, so I came in here and I hear Zaeus screaming talking about me
Saying that he hates me and shit too. So like what where's the whole narrative if if he's yelling at me and you crystal
Yeah, I want to play it you want to hear it he was already spurging a very tiny bit about us and like Kate
Wasn't he defending Brandon too?
Yes, yes, today.
That's kind of odd.
We got all of them shook for some reason.
So how does Alex reconcile that?
Is she going to befriend Zayn?
I think so to try to get her to go after me, maybe.
That would be insane.
That would be even more insane, because that's
how she's been framing all of this.
So basically, he's like, well, Brandon, he's a PDF,
and I'm a PDF, then that makes game of PDF.
Like, what?
i'm not i'm not sure how
yeah this is what
Oh, he wants to protest out your house
Wait, he just said he wants to fuck you. Uh, he's got the box
Yeah, pussy why you trying to tag somebody else in okay
Tag someone else
The monkey bitch is in a fucking another fucking state nigga. I wish I would why why do these people?
Apparently apparently we're we're monkeys. We're all monkeys in a circus
That's racist yeah
Okay, that is
Okay, he wants to protest outside your house or your dad's house. Yeah, I mean he doesn't know where I live so
Oh, he's so triggered again. I remember I had some fun fucking with this idiot. He gets so mad.
He's so mad.
I was over there for fucking two fucking days, nigga. Two days, and you didn't fucking do nothing.
What is he talking about?
I put your fucking pussy on the internet. Never fucking forget that.
I poked all of it.
He's got twenty-one.
I haven't watched Victor Deleon in like...
Don't even know
He's so bad
He's talking about me now
He'd go in with that neck beer. Damn. I know he doesn't grow fake. He doesn't go facial hair, but he
Actually, you know what I may have something I may have something okay, just let me know when you want me to pause
Yeah, I will
He says a lot worse
He took that way out of cotton. He'd use that way out of cotton
He's mad because earlier he goes and you want to call me a grandma and all this tip and you want to listen to game
On all these people and who said the fuck I'd team up with you anyway
So it just contradicts Alex even more, which is hilarious
Anything that somebody said you didn't even fucking you didn't even actually or nothing, right?
Yes, I tell Ella and why are you bringing her up?
See he hasn't changed at all
He said I'm soft earlier too, but he's so mad
Yeah, I thought that Brandon was a scapegoat for Zaya and yet here's everybody having issues with Zaya.
Wait, who is he saying he's gonna give who their next retirement? Me or you? Because we were all alone for two years. I don't know.
Who knows.
Hey, I'm gonna give you your next vacation. You never know.
Next vacation?
You fucking rubber babies, you fucking...
Me! He's talking about me!
Yeah, he's just talking out of his ass because he's mad.
He's trying to say he was gonna pull up to my dad's even when I used to live there and he never did
He had somebody from here drive outside of his fucking community. He wouldn't even go past the gate. It's just hysterical
This dude is a clown
That's the type of time I'm on nigga forever. Well, what?
Don't ask me for nothing. I
Don't care about Jonas. I'm making enough money. I'm not you who has to go live with somebody else
My pleasure, man. All right, fuck that hoe
Okay, fuck her fuck the twist your hoe
You know he okay, so the reason why I want to restream in this part is because he says something really weird about kidnapping
He has a pole which streamer would have their child kidnapped first
And one of them being Trisha Lisha's controller or I thought that Trisha and you and me were all on
Zaya's side
Well
So, I mean, she's gonna have to be blind to this shit, too
Crazy
Started this shit though and dragged our names into this again. I mean pretty much nobody was talking about Victor
But her and it's what I said. It's that it's not her kid that was targeted
It's not her doing anything but trying to make content off of him. She doesn't do shit
She just tries to make content off of the dude at least I had people like oopy make him scared of where he lived
right sake
Well, it's crazy is that he thinks that we started this no it was Alex and now
Oh, yeah, who would do a sympathy stream while they're like it. Yeah, that's still weird Viva
That's still weirdy for him to bring up someone's kids again. So Alex started all of this
I don't even know who that who is what is has I don't know they're not coming on
The thing is is I don't even Alex is the one that brought him into the brand and Q shit not us
And now he's now this guy wants to target Trisha and her kids Kate and her kid and then her kids and then
Control and well controller doesn't herself, but still like why are these guys grown-ass men targeting children?
Fuck the monkey face cake. Oh, we're fucking toes
Fuck these hoes, okay, wait what sacrifice and they hold on I'm gonna put you on full screen
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
Can you hear me? He doesn't he doesn't need to be on screen for him to talk
Yeah, no, it's all good. Yeah, real quick a NorCal was in a psych stream earlier today
When clearly we already spoke that we were gonna be on the little boycott
What's up with that?
NorCal can is a troll like I don't control them
Yeah, I don't know can't really control where people chat. You can call him an idiot for it if you want to
I don't know why we have no context of what he said in chat. You're not explain my context
Or substance. I'll be honest. I don't recall what he did say
He didn't call him out. That's what I can't remember
As far as far as I can remember he didn't call him out
No, he's like he's Syrax and got banned again
No, that's not true
Solo battery is a liar
Not saying that
We can't please people nor Cal's a troll at the end of the day
But yeah, but can we say that about most of us honestly?
Okay, there but nor Cal's not a predator
I mean this Arthur person called him out and now NorCal could be like fuck you
I didn't do there whatever and then there could be a discourse and then it's fine
But I don't think like me or Crystal could be like NorCal is that true?
What were you saying unless it was like a little bit more deep and specific like maybe if you
Was getting money and saying like fuck Crystal and these people like keep on doing what you're doing then maybe that would be
Just everyone got banned and psyched you for telling the facts about BQ then the guy correct
Yep, exactly. We just didn't just said yep. Yeah, but we again, I can't control where people go
Apparently Norkel got banned too. He got banned after I called him out in the chat
Wait
Where you went weren't you at one point psyche's best friend at one point correct there you go. You got a right at one point
So why are you trying to title on NorCal who clearly was calling out brain and cue?
Again, I'm not the internet. You use the correct term though at one point
Okay
again
Norcal which I used to call Norcal by the way, so that's where Norcal comes from
He was just clearly trolled like calling out brain and cue for his lies is what I'm being told
But did he not get banned as well today?
Eventually, I guess, but when he was there in the morning, that did not happen
What do you know at the end of the day?
At the end of the day just Jen she's been a mod there. She knows the whole truth
She knows that I have called out psych so many times
Then what does that have to do with me or what does that have to do with gamble?
We all agree that Braden Q is a fucking weirdo predator child predator
PDA has nothing to do with you. I'm just saying let's let's call out NorCal too and all of us agreed with a little
I don't a little boycott
That's fine, but I'm not gonna call NorCal out because I wasn't there to witness anything, but I will but I will
That's all I'm saying
Thank you. No problem. Thank you. Thank you. Just Jen. Just Jen was there. Thank you
Yeah, okay
Can you hear me still gamble? Yeah, nope. I got a rejoin. Hold on
okay I think I can hear now hello hello well the chat the chat will the chat
will see the truth hello crystal yeah can you hear me no oh you can't I can't
I can't hear you crystal hello
I
You might have to rejoin
All right, hold on. Okay. Are you gonna hear me? I missed I miss Arthur. God damn it
Yeah, I can hear you
So Arthur was sucking psych stick even after the Brenda thing came out, so I have no idea what he's complaining about
Yeah
Well, there you go. You got a seems like you got a barter. What do you have to say about that?
It's a constant thing with anyone hear me
Gaslighting you you're fine. Okay. Yes, you're making sure okay. Wait somebody else wants to come in Arthur
I'm here RG. What's up? What's up, brother? Well, you've been sucking Saki's cock the entire time there, buddy
Including after my thing that's friend Brendan matter of fact. I believe that you're angry because Brendan took your spot sucking his dick
That's my theory anyways. Oh
No, so so that's why I joined you know, Chris look at the brand-new drama that you've inspired
We love sucking gay man's dick. It's like his favorite thing
now so instead of avoiding instead of a question being up in the arm here I
Agree, you know, like I was always I didn't know the whole Brandon Q situation. I
Was just on Sykes panel about three or four minutes ago. I called Brandon a pedophile. It's good. So no, let me
I did bad Arthur
W there you go, so
I was unaware up until like
Cuz you're a fake
I was up. I was like maybe I
Let me know when I can ask you. What were you unaware of is a better one guy here has more testosterone than the other
That's all I'm gonna say. I'm not that's not offensive. Sometimes. It's better to be androgynous and or have more
Estrogen, so please know a sexual is what we like to call Arthur
I'm just a fly on the wall here so maybe I think like it was about maybe three
four days ago when just Jen was asking him oh excuse sorry go ahead talking to
my fiance my bub maybe three four days ago just Jen was asking him all these
questions and then psych kept going well maybe well maybe maybe maybe and it was
like whoa
Like why are you questioning with just jen is asking? Yeah, instead of answering. Why are you evading everything and
Look, I'm gonna read Keith's comment real quick. This is Arthur. Yeah, I called you multiple times last week for hanging out with psych
This is even after the branded stuff
Yes, but you have the balls to come up here and call it NorCal because he got banned in his chat
That's a little silly. I'm telling you right now. I was unaware of the whole Brandon situation
Up until I heard it myself
And just you expect us to believe that you got your nose and in it brother
You don't have to anniversary shit. You're trying to tell me you didn't know I
Don't you have you so just tell me there and then
Some foolish shit
Don't lie to us though. Don't fucking you know, think we're stupid. Come on, dude
You were fine until you came up here to call up NorCal right after you've been sucking this guy's cock for how many weeks
So you just got a mute now
I'm letting you go. I'm letting you go brother. I'm letting you go. I just kind of said what I had to say
I'm curious how you're gonna respond to be quite honest. Okay, so just Jen was asking him. Well
How are you gonna respond like when he tried to go against my?
my offspring and me and
What did say say he followed with questions and to me it's like well, that's a little weird instead of answering
Why are you evading?
You know to me that's weird
And so it kept going on and on and on and you know at one point you have to be like well
Answer the question instead of just asking questions fucking boring you'd get on with it
Okay, so
Yeah, why do you keep bringing up Jen? That's a good question so in a chat brought up what does Jen have to do with any of this?
Don't you just sit there like other way? Are you not gonna answer RG? Oh, no
I'm letting you go freezes up like a rape victim in prison like just get it over with just get it over with
Just try not to get it in my ear
I'm letting him go
Such a fag
You know, just Jen was asking him all these questions and you know, I agree
Why does think for just in though? I think she's adult and she was the one asking the questions
Okay, all the time even if she has nothing to do with it
I think you're obsessed with it. You know a couple videos out there. You're just obsessed with it. Which is weird. I
Don't even know her name to look up the video
Wait Dutchie
Why is Zaya
Threatening to show up to Gamble's house or my house to protest when Alex started all of this shit
Cuz nobody gave him a shit like that forever though. He ain't going anywhere
Very join. Hold on. We all hear you
Yeah, so yeah, he left
You'd be nice energy. Don't make me rock you. All right. That's Arthur. Not at you. I like you seem nice
Okay, thank you. Oh
Yes, that's fucking free thing. Okay. Oh storm wants to come on out. Um, so anyways, um, I'm just wondering duchy so
I said I had no beef with Zaya. I just don't condone some of the stuff. He's done. All right
I have I I'm allowed to have an opinion, but why is he threatening me because of what Alex cost? I
Don't know because he's a lunatic too, and they all
Travels
So that's duchy apparently and then just said to call him duchy. So duchy. I'm just I'm trying to
Under like why are me and gala being threatened because I like started I got a clip crystal. Okay, oh
Wait, hold on I didn't do the thing here. Okay, I'm doing it. I'm doing it. I'm doing it. I'm doing it
Think this is I think this is enough. It's only four minutes
Okay
New of Katie at 16 new of I knew of her
at 16 because Katie was doing her thing at 16.
I didn't meet her personally on a personal level
to where we're cool through social media until 17.
And she wasn't living with me until 18,
but there were things that occurred in that time
that it's a progression of events.
I hope pedophile shit happens to your children.
Am I too extreme by saying that?
Why?
I hope the pedo shit happens to you and your family.
You know, I hope that petal shit happens to your children
And I hope that one day you go to jail and you got fake petal charges on you and you get shanked up in the shower
Look at how much better I'm doing in life than you and I'm a petafile
Fucking nephews and your nieces and all that nigga my nigga. I hope they I hope they fucking butt-rape your father nigga
My nigga, I hope all that happens to you
GM until you fucking blew in the face my nigga, you're never gonna get a response from the DMs now
And why is that because the officer told me to the officer told me not to talk to you no more
But the one thing the officer said is do not communicate with him outside of the live
Okay, you know why that is gamble. That's really your fault though. The reason he said that
Want me to tell you why it's your fault because on your live stream. You was trying to make it seem as if we're friends
We're not friends money
No friends. We're not cool at all
The way you handle your live stream is you made it seem like we were friends
So the officer thinks that we working together for content. I told that nigga like I tell everybody I don't need nobody else
No
No one look at how much better I'm doing in life than you and I'm a pedophile
There's not one motherfucker out here that knows me nigga. I know me nigga
And I'm a pedophile
There's not one female that out here that knows me stop asking a fucking female about me nigga. You are whole nigga gamble you are whole nigga
Everybody keeps saying oh you scared of gamble nigga. You are home. Oh my gosh. You're not then
You're not gonna do nothing nigga. You're not gonna do nothing to me
nothing
It's a circle pass.
Wow, that's wild.
All the swatting calls, you're more than welcome to let them know now that there are two guns at HS3, two.
And I'm a pedophile.
You're not going to do nothing!
So they only need a discord.
Did he show you, did he post yours?
No, he didn't post mine.
And the crazy part is that he did mine, which was the first day that came with the swat, and then he did him the next day.
And then the next day he did me again.
a few moments later.
Yes sir.
Shhh.
Because people found out he was a pedophile. He went live and said he was a pedophile a bunch of times
Well, can you hear me still yeah, yeah, we can yeah
Yeah, I mean at this point we have I like to have supercuts when people are like
Why do you have an issue with these people? I mean, is that enough?
It chat is that enough at all for me to have a problem with him
Like any of it maybe because all I did was the first clip, right? It's a timeline
The first clip is literally showing him talk about Katie and all I said was dude
That's grooming 16 and 29 is crazy
You're weird as fuck and then the second clip is him saying he wants pedophile stuff to happen to my kids or my family
Right, and then that's that's how it that's the progression of events and then a bunch of people swat him oopy literally
Was convicted like has to is on probation for like ten years felony probation for all the swaths on him
Right, I just like
There's a grocery store that everyone in the grocery store heard
That Victor
Well, but let's no wonder he's losing his shit
So he just wants to blame you for swatting him when you didn't even swat him. It was oofy, right? Yeah, no, it was oofy
I never swatted anybody if I ever called the cops on anybody
Races
That fucking whole-ass nigga battery that lives with his fucking mama, nigga.
Called me three times from block number and try to justify her actions saying that she wasn't trying to get me
I know I was she just wanted me off the internet or remove from or away from her
But she and then she's like making it sound like I'm lying and she brought up
Saying she's gonna dox Terry. Oh, no Terry Davis whose disease is gonna get dox
And she also said there and said that she was angry when she said that but now trying to justify it basically she's trying to like pack that all right and I'm not falling for it.
Because what she said was a threat because she literally said that to Braden Q who has threatened real life people before.
And then you got this clown who Alex wants to drag us into again and she started it mentioning us.
Get your fucking life together
They're all spurting right now. It's funny
Okay, oh, I'm the new loser
But what wait a minute, but wait doesn't this make Alex a worse like not only does she choose?
Brandon Q over Trisha
Now she's gonna
Now she just got caught in a lie because I'm obviously not teamed up with this guy
And now this guy is bringing up her child even more because of Alex
At least pebs and zea don't have access to their own kids like this is wildness this is so much projection
And they want to blame everybody else for what they said online
well also
like
Etc and
Alex and these other people weren't their streams haven't been like popping lately crystal
And you think that they haven't seen you live for the past week with a couple hundred ish viewers and me on here
Repeating all this stuff that I know about them like that really upsets them a lot
So it does and the thing is
is they're only even when they're talking about me they're still having 21 viewers by people
in 20 because people would rather be here nobody wants to go into victor's chat it's a fucking it's
the worst hug box ever it's just people who will fucking suck his dick and if you say anything or
even type anything that he like takes the wrong way he'll just ban you and tell you to donate
And the weird angle he's trying to get with me and Ella, like, what does Ella think about this?
Ella knows my opinion on you. Who gives a fuck? Move on. But I'm glad I trigger you.
Cuz you're guilty
Okay, hi storm so if you notice
Gamble has been accused of being a PDF and stuff like that
Has he ever acted the way these people are losing their shit right now? No
It's also important. He like guilty people act a certain way, right?
They're so mad at me
What happened to Puffles?
I haven't seen her around.
All right, down to the fucking, the damn, what you call it, the damn swatting.
Okay, Gamble.
Would you say perfect story?
We'll see.
What happened to Puffles?
He's blaming you for swatting again, as of today.
Yeah everybody knows that we did it.
Why open the bubbles?
Hebs?
I don't know.
I don't know isn't she still with Zea?
I have no idea.
Okay, I don't know anything about peps
Wait, he just referred himself to Aaron Carter like these people are weird because and I'm not Aaron Carter
No, I rather have Aaron Carter alive than you. Well, not a lot like that. Wait, man
Let me retry that statement. I'm much rather be streaming Aaron Carter over this guy like you're nobody
At least Aaron Carter was a somebody
I see you it's gonna get aggressive and I hope that you have that energy
I'm gonna fucking pop your shit like the nigga that popped you you remember, right? Oh, he's talking about you gamble
My god, he's branding cute 2.0
And then you think that the fucking keyboard and the Internet's gonna save you yeah, maybe
Don't be one day
Alex said I threatened her but these people are threatening us
How many times do they have to replay you?
You know whatever in that little fight thing and you got jump like and they think it's cool to jump people
Okay, they sound like ski mask Andy
I mean, I don't care what anybody says who's like actually not really so weird. I don't understand like water. Let me pop you
Let me fight you
Game fight like what the but he he's just shouting like to see he's self soothing right now
He's not going anywhere. He literally just said chill with yo ho chill with yo ho one day one day the tables are gonna turn on you
He needs a pacifier
Probably
See, I told you he's scared of my dad's gate. I don't even live there anymore
They all call me that you know, it's funny is like I've never referred to myself as a pedophile
And all of them do and from their perspective all I've done is hunted them so I don't understand why they call me that
i know because that's what the thing i said that on my stream earlier i said
gamble's never stopped there and said he goes after petto's and petto's always
he doesn't associate himself with petto's so how does that make him a petto owner
because he calls y'all out when y'all bring him up he doesn't he's not friends with y'all he never was
these people are they want to wear his skin okay you guys are fucking pathetic
you don't know who to you choose who you ever do the use he's in he's saying this in carti lee's
I'm sorry what's pathetic, huh?
This is fucked up
He said a brandy Q is a fucked up human being and then I'm a fucked up human being then that makes game
Well, just as bad as us and why what now he's saying Alex is just as bad as as them
What I mean, that's true, but what about me is so much like say and Brandon, please or Alex
Nothing, I think the only thing that any of us have in common is that we've streamed
Yes, I don't really consider their streaming the same as my
Right
And then he had the nerve to post like a photo of me from alive from 2020
when clearly yeah everyone knows that um i i heavily filtered my pfp over here like
but i've shown my face off camera on camera the fact they want to go out looks whatever
crystalline you're a fucking he's mad because he wants me to turn against you gamble
plain and simple i'm gonna do you but that's fine you made your choice i'm not worried about that
you made your choice crystal you chose me instead of him
He wants problems with me
Hey, I think things have been going well over here
He likes doing that
Who's gonna defend you myself?
It's so weird
He always does this he always says he's gonna pull up on a woman
He literally just said he will not pull up on my elderly father
But he'll go in front of your house and make himself look retarded cuz I was up with that
I live in a different state. He's a lot like Brandon. He likes to target women and then cry about men
Wow, these are like he fixates on women. There's a reason those are my last two targets when I was a YouTube streamer
Was Victor De Leon and Brandon Quintana. He's asking for my address right now
That's crazy. It's crazy
But he doesn't know that I have a neighbor that's a cop that can literally be like, you know, you're disturbing the peace
Do you know what's disturbing the people? You never have to worry about Victor De Leon
If he ever came to your house, he would be out there and you could literally just call the police on him.
He has a history of doing this.
Good thing I live in HOA, because he'll be removed from the neighborhood for trespassing with threats.
You know, it's literally just harassing somebody clips him asking for the fucking address and then a cop shows up
But she says this guy was asking for my address online and then showed up
He's not gonna he's not gonna wave
He's not gonna be able to use his first amendment rights outside of your home when you say that he specifically went there
Right from a different state. I mean see the other thing about Florida is different because if you do that in Florida
And you have clips of the person threatening you you can literally just shoot them
So that's another I can do that
My property I can do the same
probably
I mean, here's the thing. The thing is, is as long as you have evidence of them being
threatening and police show up and there's a dead body and you have a recording of them
threatening you, it's like pretty cut and dry. How that works. That's why I keep, that's
why I keep the video of Brandon saying, Hey, William, when I'm going to come and put a
bullet in your head, because if I ever see Brandon Q, I can just do whatever I want because
You got I mean right like quote unquote in here scared, but I'm not scared like I like honestly when you do that
You'll be behind bars. You'll be arrested and who's gonna give a fuck about you
Oh, you're gonna be homeless because you think Artie's gonna take you back
None of the show look look Jen says that she'll get her baby daddy to defend you ski mask pull up
He's he's close by he'll do it
That would actually be hilarious
Two out of his mind to drive anywhere. No, he'll do it. No, no, we'll send him a little we'll send him like 200 bucks
Don't catch a charge
Like these people are a look he goes and but the funny thing is is Zaya aka Victor
He literally just said and bitch. This is the unit who's gonna protect you
But he's the one wanting to go real life. Oh, who's gonna protect me the law
Oh, yeah, no David Dekou would physically beat the shit out of Victor Deleon Victor Deleon is like malnourished
And David Dekou is like a little bit old, but he's scrappy enough. He's great. He's got a screw loose
Well, I don't have any beef with ski to be honest. He hates Alex. I
Don't like ski, but he wouldn't want oh
Gosh, I really don't want him knowing where I live, but at the same time it comes to it like
Nice. Oh, there you go. Yeah. Well, he's got a reason. Yeah. He's why does Victor talk about everyone's kid?
He and Brandon get exposed for being predators and then their their response is to double down and say if I am a pedophile
Then do something so what I want that to happen to your family and then they just start doing all that crazy shit
That's crazy. It's fucked up. I think that's funny
But then Karen sent me a two boys most crystal. Nobody's threatening you
I don't want you on the live, but these are the people he associates himself with Victor. I don't look my job with you is done
It's following you forever. I don't even bring you up. You should probably blame Alex for bringing you into all of this shit
I said I said Alex is but he he wants to bring blame us what when Alex brought him up to you
And try to do a weird weird thingy like nobody gave a fuck about this guy
But but but Victor you are a weird pedophile and going to control his kids school is like crazy dude
That is anyways. Yeah, 1629 is crazy and
Yeah
You're not gonna come outside. You're not gonna get you're not gonna you see now
And then can you hear me still gamble yep, okay, so imagine this okay
I had the now there's clips of you saying, you know, you're a PDF you support Brandon Q is a PDF
And there's children in my neighborhood, so
You're gonna be escort pretty bad. So coming here would be a really stupid move a panel to my face
You know, I just said I would by your own words. I would play your own words against your own protest
The controller is big and bad. She don't even say pillow to my face
I said I just thought it was very pretentious or like you're the one that called yourself a pedo
Why is he bragging about a woman being scared that he showed up
He wants you to say it to his face
And you quite frankly discussing the pedal thing is funny to y'all. That's what it is. It's funny to y'all
Okay, I would wish this on you, but I don't think I don't think pedophilia is funny
He just wished a pedophile on me, but all but all I have is rubber babies
Yeah, that's see here we go
I took I just played a clip of him saying that two years ago, and he's saying the same shit and
Everybody questions my fucking methods. I don't get it. I don't even have the rubber babies anymore
At this point, I think if nobody agrees with the fucking evidence that I propose I honestly think that they're retarded
Yeah, I'm sorry
I just like with the Brandon the Brandon fucking clip packet versus the ETC clip packet
If anybody watches those for 15 seconds and doesn't immediately think that they're weird as fucking don't want to talk to them
You're retarded. I
Who's gonna buy
Who's gonna buy Zaya's shoe collection for him to be able to afford to come out here
Wow
Yes, but why are you trying to great me is weird. Oh
Fucking fish baby. Let me tell you another big bitch. All right, this one definitely
I had in the back of my mind, but I said I don't want to be rude
Bitch, what's up with your fucking filters?
No, it's better than your neck neck beard and it's better than your clown-looking hair just saying I
mean
So you're just jealous of that liquid, okay
Where is this hoe?
Where's this hoe at? What the fuck is this?
What the fuck is this?
Oh, he's gonna play old streams of mine. So this is what he's showing now
Have you lost your fucking mind, what the fuck is this I have to heavily tell me so I
Don't attract
How does that man talk about how anybody looks no clue
Let me remind you that clip was from like
2020 that he showed you are so many men's type. Okay, not mine
Yeah, but I'm sure a lot of other people I have a man, and I'm taking and I'm very happy. There you go. I
Don't understand like the fiance says he looks like leprechaun from the movie leprechaun
Yo, Salute, knew your dad on the check and they got us pregnant.
We outside, I see you on the floor, I don't know.
Okay, Crystal, you could call them ghetto.
That's fine.
Huh?
I said you could call them ghetto. They're they're actually ghetto
They are with that clown looking hair. They look like Ron and like Donald leprechauns
Yeah, any
Misty so guy who like pretends to be black, but he's not fully black
But he's dark and then hates black people and hates white people and he's got the Joker
No idea I ain't keeping up with
People knew your dad is that played? No
Who is that dude, I don't know some random dude he's talking about you though
Okay, I'm sure they all are
Somebody needs to
All right, do you think do you think he knows that the house he's living in in the next room? There's my merch
Do you think Cardi wears the DX merch like around the house like or do you think she doesn't do it while he's there because she doesn't want to upset him?
The second like what you just said
Victor you should thank me for the home because Cardi would have known who you are and
And for this guy to judge who would I look like I wouldn't want to touch him with a 10-foot pool
Yeah, I probably act I actually yours is tight
So that's me probably is bitter about this as well too
Okay, wait a minute wait a minute. We're anti-racist and this guy is white the one in the bomb that just showed
He's white saying that yeah, but they're all they're all from different places in New York
So they all say that
Cuz you could be you could be white presenting and have one like Dominican or Puerto Rican
Like cousin and then say nigga and they'll let it slide. So
They want full on this thing. Nobody's making him famous. He's making himself look like a fool. I'm telling you
This is not a good. This is a fucking channel killer
to try to defend yourself against this to try to combat those
Media packets that were made two years ago of shit that they both still do
Yeah, actually impossible. The only thing that they could do is continue to create
Toxic circle jerk of people who are dumber than them or people who are okay with it
So now you know that for two years anybody going into victor's chat has seen all of that
They're all okay with that behavior. Now, you know who to avoid. It's like super simple
It's a standardized test. I don't know
I kind of want to fast-forward some of this because he's just all in my legs
Nobody gives a fuck
I only plan to come in for a little bit and show those clips and then I stayed because I saw him on here
But you enjoy your stream crystal
I may come back in a little bit if other people want to come on and help her stuff you do that. All right
I want to see if he's bringing me up again
Okay, let's go.
Best forwarding it.
Okay.
Let's talk about court.
What's this?
Huntsville, Texas, more shit.
What the fuck am I watching?
from Justice. Hi Q. Hi little brother.
What's up little bro? Wasn't there just somebody else up here?
Campbell. Yeah, where'd he go?
He just wanted to play those one's clips and he said if anybody else wants to do
him they can't. Why, you want to talk to him?
Anyways, how was your day Q?
I think if Gamble has anything to say about me, he needs to say it's in my fucking face.
How about that?
What?
You're kidding.
No, I'm just fucking around.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Anyways, so...
Don't give me a bat's what I thought.
Like, you're gonna do anything.
Hit you with the door.
Yeah, I'll fucking stop it with my foot.
Yeah, you know Alex took us like when we were just being playful and threatening each other with like doors and stuff
She took that and decide to lie and say I threatened her to have her
Face hitting but I never even had to do that
She did it on her own on a bike because she had a curb and went face down
Like I get that I fell off the electric scooter, but those are more intense. I remember that
Yeah, but but those things are dangerous a bike a bicycle though a bicycle
They should have never let you on a fucking electric scooter in the first place. I'm gonna do it again
I want I'm gonna be in bubble wrap and a helmet. I want to learn
I just put you in like a fat suit or something. I
Don't know what the link this is X.com Twitter link
Okay, I P2 always win. No, what the hell is that?
No, the thing is is
again Alex
One
So Alex's weird angle was to get Zaya to go and gamble to fight to get Brandon and Q to fight
But gamble has gone for two years. I was gone for two years. She just wanted to throw my name in the mix
and now people are
That Joker shit is so played out like yeah, you're the Joker by the way, that's such a played out corny gimmick like
Everybody thinks they're the Joker just like he
You ever heard of Sin City Manning Carter like we have psyche once he wishes he was Aaron Carter
We guys know he wishes he was Howard Stern
Psyche wants to be Howard Stern. He says this all the time. He thinks of himself as like Howard Stern or something
It's weird, but have you ever heard a fucking Sin City Manning before?
You're familiar with that crystal, huh? Are you familiar with Sin City Manning?
Like Sin City the game
No, no, no, it's a streamer. His name is Sin City Manny. Anyways, this is this is this guy that Zay has been trying to like emulate him
basically
He listen he
He had a beef with another youtuber that other youtuber went to Las Vegas where Manny does IRL
And he was doing IRL there and Manny came out there when he was doing IRL with a gun and shot him right on live
Streaming killed him and his wife
Zaya's fucking sick ass is trying to like emulate that dude because he used to walk around dressed up in the Joker paint and when
Zaya learned about that story. He thinks now he's like Sin City Manny like if somebody comes up to me
I'm gonna shoot him or something
right
He wants if you haven't heard about that. It's a pretty fascinating case, but yeah, he's in jail right now
This happened like last June
But yeah, he's fucking one streamer was streaming on the Las Vegas Strip fucking man
He just comes up with a gun and you see it on camera
shoots and dead right on stream on YouTube I
Don't understand these people are so like weird like
They take the internet way too seriously, but then they incriminate themselves and then they incriminate themselves again and then again
Like I did people are like, you know Chris will be careful as a he showed up at Alex's house. I
Don't give a fuck
Well, I mean if he does that to you it's just a pattern of behavior at that point and I'm pretty sure the cops won't be happy so
No
Weird and Matt. I don't know how the motherfuckers getting away with what he's getting away with now because I mean he keeps pulling up on
Controller he just gets away with it. He could just do whatever the fuck you want
And who knows maybe, you know, this will fall back on Karen because maybe she hired him as a hitman to come after me
Baby, thank you. We have Alex and we have this guy and they they're all all suspects of being a current hitman to go after my life
and
I don't know if anybody that that actually goes to people's places to protest that they're not a pedo because of some internet shit
That honestly makes them look more stupid to do
Bay clips, why are you so fucking far up my ass fuck you seriously get your tongue out of my ass
Anyhoo
I'm starting to think big clips is chicken cakes
No, definitely not
Yeah, I think that's just chicken chick chicken cakes alter ego like I mean I get like people seem
Like I should be scared of this guy because he goes real life, but I'm not scared one bit at all
like
What because he hasn't done anything yet? I'll be scared
Hey
So someone sent me a video of gamble pissing say off so bad. He's like almost crying. You want to watch it? It's like 13
Yeah, yeah, all right. I'll share it. Give me one second. Okay. I think I remember this. I
Haven't seen it yet, so I don't know
Sounds familiar. That's the one there it is
All right, let me play
Did I hit play yeah, I did
Hello
He's such an ugly-looking motherfucker holy shit
He talks about other people in the way they look
Crazy someone that looks like him should not pass
He looks even worse than this like this is nothing. He looks way worse now
Oh
They had a really like a fucking really toxic like abusive one when he first went to live or when she first went to live with him
And then over time they kind of got cooler
What's up with the weird eyebrows, is it like the, the squint part in the movie?
It's somebody's mom and dad, just think about that.
He looks like a large toddler with a, a, a, a load in his diaper.
That's what he looks like to him.
Not a tough guy.
He's like a bitch.
One main show, Monica.
I'm toast to me.
I'm a, I tell the truth, nigga.
You're a liar.
He's a tough guy with that Hellcat gun he's got
This is gonna be like what a hundred pounds ago for pebs poor thing
Yeah, pebs ages like fucking five years every one year
Like milk
You should have seen her when she first came around. She wasn't have bad looking when she first first started streaming like two years before this
Man, I'm getting all the content
So Gavill said that peps invited me to Zayas house without even asking him that's pretty
This dude used to ruin all of his content just letting fucking music ruining everything
I
What is he doing that's drugs for y'all he needs to get his fucking phone ip banned off this board
She thinks she's bad as fuck, bro
She's just making her bingo wings dance
Literally looks like she ain't herself now
I'm pretty sure they're getting all dressed up to sit in front of a fucking live stream like going and doing your make up, getting all done.
Fucking lame.
Then you see her nowadays whenever they go and they were stalking control and she looks like she just came out of bed, she's in fucking pajamas.
Died, but inside, this is what they do.
How old are they?
It would bet it's bad if you should pick all of his sneakers and put them on a pile.
I think in this peps is like 33 and Zayah is like 43, but now I think Zayah is like 45 and Pez is 35.
Wait, Zayah's in his 40?
Zayah's 45. Zayah's 45. Zayah was like 42 when I met him. That was like three years ago.
Boy ass nigga.
Zayah's got kids.
They've got sons that are like in their 20s like grown-ass
You niggas can't read no paperwork, but you're talking about fake pedophiles. So cool. I'm a fake pedophile nigga. Pull up to my fucking ass.
And you know what?
Now, one of you fucking fact-
Nobody's afraid of you, dude.
Nobody.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're gonna fuck me my fucking son.
Fuck you.
Fuck the NorCal.
One time and they gave him fucking bruises off camera.
Not on NorCal.
In his pedophile comment, I said, ask them.
My nigga, you're not gonna do nothing!
Somebody's triggered!
You're gonna sit by your fucking computer like a faggot!
Or on Reckon Island.
He's so mad!
You're gonna sit by your computer-
You'll be mad, little pedophile.
Nothing, nigga.
You hear?
Not one nigga ever done something to me, nigga.
I didn't even pull up to my address, nigga.
And they shit is sweet, nigga.
They is addressing it.
You niggas is pussies on the internet, nigga.
Fuck outta here.
I say it, not me, gamble.
No, this is two years ago at Bake Loops.
This is way before Curry Lee's house
Never coming back
This reminds me of that guy like
No
Wow
You've never seen whenever he busted through the door trying to get after her that door behind him is broken in this
Of course juice does
That is the community that just comes from these fucking sneaker chimps with him. That's his daddy
NorCal you could suck my fucking dick
Most of the people who come from his community don't fuck with him besides like maybe saman juice and a couple other little
Cockriders that you'll find over there. If you do you're gonna ask for a fucking picture
You're not going to pull up with no smoke talking that grooming shit kind of
It's kind of just a little feeling nigga, just a little itty bitty feeling yelling like that
She's five one and when he stands up next to her they're about the same height so
You should be happy that you even here, bro. I'm gonna keep it a hundred with you. You should be happy
A real tough guy. You can just tell
Happy that you even here, bro
I'm gonna keep it a hundred with you. You should be happy to be here. I'm a real tough guy. Look at me
Yeah, he got a few cold members
Fucking Kalama
Smokey fuma
I love this because this is what he does
This is the type of person we could all get in unison behind
Fuck stop mentioning my fucking name
Stop mentioning my fucking name
You can't talk for me
You're a liar you can't talk for me
Nigga
And anybody out here that thinks that pepsi talks for me you are fucking dummy nigga, and I'll tell you to your fucking face
Put your fucking hand up in the chat and say hey
I talk for myself and they're going to do nothing to me.
Yeah, G6, the low cows doing the low cow things.
Fuck that nigga, I don't know what he done in the past.
Suck my dick, nigga! You got a problem nigga, you asked me!
This is why this community is even where it's at in the first place because that fucking idiot
pebs decided to go and live with him and now our world's collided with that fucking retard sneaker community.
Fuck your mother, nigga! Fuck outta here! I talk about all this shit I want to on this motherfucker!
Yeah, it is on HingeKate.
Tell me the time out, nigga!
Hey, we tough guys when it comes to the ladies, huh? Talks of pebs like that.
You fucking talk, man! I talk to myself!
It's all fucking weak shit, dude.
Who the fuck is the matter with y'all?
Who looks back at me?
That's what you think, bro.
Are you sabotaging me?
The only good thing we got from the ETC merger is Arthur
Wow
Yeah, that's what they say
I did I did RG do you have the do you have the video of him saying like I knew of her and all that that whole thing?
No, I do know I don't pay attention to this guy. No, no, no, no, no, I'm just saying
I know you have a lot of shit probably
Nothing, okay, so one
I figured we'd play it up here. That's all I need to find
The whole scene is only nine thing. Yeah
Because I fucking I had a posted on my channel lost my channel, so I don't have access to it anymore
He already played it before and then barb was at a grocery store. It should be played every day
It should be played every day like a fucking national anthem
Like when I came from Marty's and all that like I didn't even know this panel stuff existed
But I knew who he was and I knew he was a fucking sicko groomer
So Marty's found out really fucking quick and he was really smart about it
So I'll give Marty that because he was like, oh, I see this motherfucker just wants the attention
He wants the calls he wants the fucking knocks and he was just like I'm not giving it to him and moved on
Watches chimp chimp oh
I didn't ask
Right eventually you got to use your fucking ears niggas stop running your fucking mouth nigga the reason you hear
Wow
Oh my god, did you just hit her?
He busts the door down when he was all pissed off at her trying to like
It's gone worse than that
This is parties house the closet. No, no, no, no, no, this is this is way way
This is back when Zaya actually lived on his own
You hear what he said I'm the headliner
Right now y'all
Baby tough guy
I
Was laughing
Threatening me for what Alex is the one that brought you up not gamble not me was Alex
You should probably leave us alone. Yeah, but you people then why would anyone waste their time on you dude? Come on
Alex brought you into it not me
You're 40 years old you can't even keep a roof over your head
But you didn't do anything.
Well, come on, dude.
Let's go.
So much shit about me and my situation in my bread.
Look at you now, nigga.
Look at you now.
You live with Pebs.
You live with Pebs and Cardi Lee's house.
Fuck out of here.
You live in a fucking.
You live in somebody's bedroom in their crib.
Pebs, if you ever pisses you off or lays your hands on you,
take all of his sneakers, put them in the bathroom or bleach on them.
That's that's one way to you know, get him back
Poor bleach all over those sneakers
My issues with Brandon Q. I would just hand over your chat to be honest. I am he doesn't get a voice here
Fuck him. I got no gurus allowed
I just wanted him to skirt out a little bit while we're playing and I'm doing this. My show nigga
Fuck you talking about nigga. I'm the star in the show. I'm the star
What a fucking cornball
Get hold of
You don't get any money either, dude, apparently.
The only reason he was getting money is donations because of what he was doing.
Can't even keep a roof over his fucking head.
It's sorry this beaker market
Business
desserts are selling
Yeah, there's a part two so we don't want that to
Kali tomorrow. Okay. I'll wait. I'm looking forward to the day. She leaves look at them
My
What the situation is now hearing him talk like this is hilarious
Such a loser such a mr. Big ball and over here. Yeah, you were big ball in back fucking three years ago
Weren't you bitch?
Big ball in three years ago
All right, let me get part to your bear. It is like
I don't know if I can hear are y'all talking
Yeah, I did talk. Yeah, let me go and this week. I might begin to whip to wait till I flex that on that punk as beach
Never mind
Fuck ass motherfuckers. I just I just loved about you sit there and talk so much shit
Call me a bun say this say that you live in the fucking addict with pebs now, nigga. I love that shit
You say you're so much shit
Twice you're exactly he's old enough to be my dad legitimately. He's like fucking 18 years older than me
You should be in a better place
Don't I can't believe he came into my chat. Well, he said he's that salty crystal
I would say this is a crystal W folks. This is a
You got all that
entire crystal
Triggered to because we said he looked kind of looks like psyche
Yeah, the best part about the damage is already done and he doesn't have to make any mistakes. It's already there
He's already fucked it all up.
He already pissed it all the way.
Not for kids, folks.
Y'all can ban phone pays.
I don't give a fuck.
There's not one female that out here that knows me.
Stop asking a fuck.
New of my old apartment.
I knew of it.
Everybody keeps saying, oh, you scared the gamble.
Nigga, you are ho!
You're not going to do nothing!
You're not going to do nothing, nigga.
Cuttin' promos is what we love to go on.
Nothing!
Yeah, he's, yeah, for real.
Cuttin' promos for gamble.
Imagine me.
Yeah, I miss cuttin' promos.
I haven't cut a promo in three days.
You're not going to do nothing, nigga!
Your secret powers come through the internet!
To the internet my nigga, okay through the internet Sean face. He brought me up because of Alex
I still can't believe he used the balls of cotton on anyone's looks
On the internet talking about me nigga, which is to my benefit. You're such a star
He has like a fucking an unlimited cow like he never even when he's happy he looks mad
He's a giant star. What are you talking about you? I don't believe you. He should just fucking do God
This man just relax Victor calm down
But hands and feet on me.
Fuck this internet shit.
You niggas is pussy.
How are you 45 year old man?
He must not eat the bread crust.
RZ, I know what it is.
He didn't eat the crust on the bread like his mama told him
to, and that's why his fucking beer digger went.
He can drink the milk.
I waited every day.
He didn't eat the crust on the bread.
That's why his beard's all fucked up.
I see.
I thought it was because of autism.
Nobody's showing up.
That's what dad always told me when I was younger. He was like, you better eat the crust or else you're not gonna
You know what he just said? Nobody show it up. You're still a big tough guy because nobody's showing up
Why would anyone waste gas money on you?
Honestly, God, dude, who would waste five dollars worth of gas on you? You retarded midget
You're rooming sicko fuck. You know, you know what that is crazy to think about like even if he likes
was still making what he would like doing how as good as he was back then
He's still like I mean there ain't no longevity in streaming unless you got
He still didn't do nothing. They still didn't come put up. No, it's gonna work. I don't find on you
Why waste your time?
How do you have a channel with 26,000 subs and you only get 26 viewers?
Like this is a very time I'm really sad.
Somebody please tell me that.
It's sad.
And even if you had 120, the different, like the retention rate there, 120 compared to
a 26,000 on your whole channel?
He knows
Viewers on a I could pull 20 viewers right now honest on a fucking channel with 200 subs right now
Couple sneaker chips holding on
So it's any calls the cops more than xyrax
I don't know
He looks like a little sick to me anyway
Barry says it's a dead channel
Sounds like you failed
When I put out his fucking the apartment that he moved to after this I doxed it first like I got the information in doxed
Everybody was still mad at me. You ain't mad at me no more
You fucking know that your fucking ears is working. How cute. How can you do that today? Oh my god?
You're dunking him in heavy so top cue you should be nervous and scared right now because he's just that tough
So scary look. I've been going out at what this dude for a long time
That shirt is so gay
So gay and he doesn't know what to tell him that a he's not tough. He looks like a fake
Cuz he only keeps yes man around
That's a fact
I don't need no fucking female. I want you. I don't need you. Don't fucking play yourself
Oh, yeah, you don't scare a few other females you pussy because Marty knew how to play the fucking game the right way
This is wild.
This guy plays the game the opposite way.
This is the first time I've ever seen like Zaya clips, by the way.
Look at every laugh.
Every laugh is a little loser.
Every point in the setup.
Nobody's laughing with you, you little midget.
I don't give a fuck!
Screaming at the door, by the way.
Intimidating a woman, you know.
Totally unhinged.
I don't give a fuck.
Fuck out of here, and this is sober too by the way. I'm pretty sure they're sober or at least he is
I don't think I don't think he's drinking pezzes
Even if he's not sober y'all tell he's not trashed. He's not like blacked out drunk or anything. He's perfectly well aware of what's going on
Well, that's how we do it.
Well, we have this thing I need a stream of Brain and Cube
because he just started his.
Do you want me to pause this?
No, you've got him to play it for now, until he's first.
Let me know.
We'll just play both at the same time,
so we'll clean the phone.
He can retream old clips of Crystal all he wants.
We've all seen that shit.
Like, I don't think he realizes what we're doing around here.
We actually watched his shit live.
Yeah.
No one cares. This is a huge crystal W right here. What's getting this fellow angry?
He's probably sitting over there with fucking 20 viewers crying and we're over here fucking maxing them out
You nothing but a lion-ass female a lion-ass female
Crystal just came back to this is just the beginning
No respect out of here, nigga. You don't show no respect nigga
Out of everything in that room the only thing he has left is that little case
The only thing he has left is that little case with the hats. That's it
Triples day as viewers
By the way, uh, RG, you were right about crime man, um, being a liar.
Yeah, everybody's drop a like on Crystal's dream.
Thank you though.
Drop a like on Crystal's dream.
Thank you.
You're obligated to.
Introduce.
Introduce to the queen.
Oh, we're being reached by Brandon Q. Let me type in Brandon Q loves kids. Hold on.
All right, hold on. Let me pod this.
He's reaching us, so we're gonna go and play Brandon Q loves kids again.
Brandon Q is a pedophile, a pedophile, a pedophile.
I did that in Sikes, I didn't care for it very much.
These guys sound so similar.
Well, you know, it's a sicko type.
I've been meaning to talk to Oliver because I got time to watch out.
Brandon's been looking for him.
So BSM says I heard the value of Jordan's tank to also he's probably down 50% on his sneaker portfolio
The fact that the word sneaker portfolio is a thing makes me sick
I mean, let's be honest or Jimpy as it is people still make hella money doing that just not him
I don't know man. I know nothing about it. You can make I mean
They can if you if you're dedicated enough to and you know what you're doing people do make a lot of money with that fucking shoe
Shit, you know, but you don't think you're not making that much buddy
The thing is is branding queue is re-streaming when gamble was on my stream. So he's a little delayed right now
So I got you go we go back to the video then
I think you could let branding queue restream you why not whenever he gets to this part
I don't even well all he's doing is giving you traffic from shorts like he has his streams on shorts
You know people are just gonna watch his short stream over here. Fuck it. That's some down is when you play the youtube brainy Q loves
See Ben Gleck is correct here. I nearly don't think you're dead trading card games are king right now. That's the fact
play the day clip is what jad said, but it's you're sure
we can play the day clip
that's always been a thing
but I will after the day clip I will play the brand new
say the cards has changed
there used to be baseball cards now it's, are we getting on
hmm
you can't get out no clothing store
can't get out no clothing store
welcome to my world
it ain't about no Saturdays or no Sundays
We'll use the bathroom upstairs, bro.
Okay, I popped Bailey.
The pub's gotta take a giant shit.
He's not even bigger than the TV.
Bro, he's barely as tall as the TV that's sitting on his bro.
Look at that. Look at the difference in size
between him and some of the shit around you.
Tiny.
Look at him compared to that. That's a short bed.
Wait, watch him go near the doorway.
Look at how small he is near the doorway.
New name is so tiny. Oh, yeah, that's a good one pixel
Well, I'm only like two inches away from the top of the door
I
room upstairs. Go use the bathroom upstairs. Go use the bathroom upstairs. Fuck you in your phone.
Fuck you in your phone. Get your phone and get out. Do what you gotta do. Go. Leave. Bye.
Oh, and now imagine that he was a party and now he's gonna be more triggered by Campbell because
of Alex. Imagine them going homeless to this party. I'm not asking you for a favor. You asking me for a favor.
Alright, my ass is straight. Go find your own phone and leave. Yeah, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave. Bye, leave.
Look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him
Hey, barricade the door because of Petra, it's wild.
I've noticed every one of these guys like to bring up Aaron Carter.
Like, what?
Yeah, look, you and Chad, I see that.
Yeah, somebody was adding me in that chat.
I just got placed to add boy music.
Yeah, I'm so excited.
I got into a fight with my girlfriend.
We had all even
16-year-old clip
A lot of us didn't even know about that shit
domestic violence wreaks him sad, folks
Oh now I have a roasting sun for him. I'll do gonna I'm gonna sing the girl version of this song
There you go, Crystal because he's crying like a bitch
Like a little bitch
Oh look it's Fatso.
Surprise surprise.
This is where Ron comes from too.
Why am I shocked?
Ron used to be Zeya's number one dick sucker when he had the same amount of viewers as Sandman has now.
He just had to jump to Sandman's because now Sandman has the viewers.
Sandman basically hijacked all of Zeya's like viewers.
That's why he took all the sneaker monkeys to his shit.
Well, so Ron jumped over with him
You gotta be I mean hey look I hate Samman, but I'm much I like Samman more than
Samman's more annoying though infinitely but as they as a worse person
By far
What exactly is he winning?
Kalama 420
Kalama is one of his little dick-sucking cult members
Yeah, well you'll see he must have him stuck to dick
I would love to see that
He's stuck to hell a dick
Kalama's fucking neck is always stuffed with his ass
Fuck
He's 40 years old and can't even keep a roof over his head
What is he winning?
I want actually juice runs into the wall. It might be
That guy's life is the most entertaining he's ever been ever I
Don't know so I can't
But who could ever say that guy went on
I don't even know what the context is of this, so it was just a far too weird looking legs
of I'll say that this must be back when they had things
Well, I wouldn't want to be that girl either
Schumann says that it's a woman who's been abused
His brand is tarnished. He'll never be a big youtuber
soon you're going to have to go get a job oh my god you're going to have to go get a
job you only got to play it because it's X times a week it's coming now that's something
I just see him getting triggered like this now
And I'm tearing party
So I gave it a jazzy you see you always wait exactly what has the one
Yeah, I would like to see the list RG. I was selling you a minute ago. He has a few cult members
That's one of his biggest ones as it
Kalama 42
There's a couple of them that he has they're not they don't join panels
They don't really talk, but they don't they stuck dick a lot. They're good at that
They're just like chat little fucking you know and over there I kind of like that dude. He's always they're like
They're like these they're like his KZ's. They're his KZ's. That's the best way I could put it. I
got you
The KZ really dire where you trolling he's dead. She's probably in there sad. What's his name? Can I look it up?
Even current
Even currents of what what Boston
Because sometimes it's hard to tell with you
Even me even a seasoned veteran like me sometimes. I don't know when you're fucking with me
Give me a second. I'll put it in the bag
I mean it would make sense though because he hasn't been around and you know
He doesn't really stay away that long. It's fucking homeless. I mean of course to make some
No, I mean it makes you make sense that he's not around cuz he would have joined a panel or went live or did something by now
You can't even dance to ballet
This is what I think
I think this is a domestic violence too
That's not how you do it about life
And nobody even talks about how he used to fuck
because she was dreaming and so forth
I mean, this is a deniture of the houses
This does look like a nice thing
I imagine he couldn't hold on to it, right?
So this was two place this was two places ago, and no he ended up so when he had a falling out with his
with his
His act so he was using keep on second. So I can talk this. I actually should price it is this important
Yeah, you got a lot
No, they go boom when he had a when he had a falling out with his ex
He was using his exes like so like to co-sign with him for all these places, right?
Because his credit is absolutely destroyed from not paying child support
He had like 80 grand racked up in child support. He didn't pay. He just said fuck it for years
So he has
grown-ass kids that can go to the bar and drink and he
He you know fucked up his credit. He was using her
Using her social security her co-sign social security number whatever you want to say your credit to get these places
And then one day he found out that he was babysitting her babies her kids his stepchildren
While she went and fucked some other dude from YouTube community how to falling out with it with her
And then she wasn't going to co-sign for shit anymore.
So then he got that fucking idiot.
Jade is to co-sign that last place in that big, that, you know,
that big place, the one that I doxed with the pool and everything.
That real nice place.
Oh, he did that.
And you know, it's funny the way he lost that place.
He couldn't pay the he couldn't pay the lease anymore.
He ran out of, you know, he stopped popping.
He couldn't pay it.
So now he lives with Cardi Lee.
That's hilarious.
And in the attic by the way always winning Q this guy's always winning big baller
So the comments say nobody confirmed him confronted him about that. He denied it
And then we had proof and he tried to walk him back. He said nobody's on the lease with him. It's got it
Yeah, there's no way he's there's no way he's gonna be able to get a
Lease on a place with his credit score all fucked up like that. Yes, he moves places like every year
Wow
We can finish the clip you got it you got it
She's not even doing anything that's why I was talking there's like three minutes, so
Yeah, he's streaming her downstairs just making money off her being drunk dancing
He's literally living in a viewer's closet right now
He's living in literally a viewer's closet, that's crazy
The fact and shout out to her too cuz I still like her
She's got a heart of gold. Shout out to Cardi Lee. I'll never I'll never stop fucking with Cardi Lee
I don't know what the hell you were thinking letting that fool into your house, but it's not in the business
I don't know her, so I can't tell you anything. I'm sure she's nice, but you'd have to be be nice
No, she's a great lady. She's I mean, you know, she's trust me. She's awesome. She's super fucking. She's got a hard of gold
Trust me, but I don't know what the hell she was thinking letting him in there. You know, and that he was just gonna
Should travel. Oh my god. What is now he's trying to go to war with people like what happens with like when if it's not me?
Like what happens to somebody who doesn't give a fuck about Cardi Lee and they just
docks, they just keep doxing the shit out of you and sending the sending shit to your house,
you know, like, what is this comment mean Q or was it the period blood on the sidewalk?
Oh, yeah, one day. Okay. So at that place that we're watching right now
Pebs went out one day to smoke a cigarette or something and she left her fucking pad and blood and shit on the
On the walkway and Zaya came out and filmed it and shit and we all do it. It was so nasty
You can ask anybody about this. She literally squatted down to smoke a cigarette and she like bled and left the pad outside
He humiliated he humiliated that came to talk
He humiliated his peps for no reason at all. That's not cool
No, I mean it was it was like I don't even I don't even think that he like it was something that he was trying to do
I think that they just went outside like they were going to leave
And they were taking the camera to go IRL and he just was like what the fuck is that like I don't even think
I hope he used to hope it didn't happen like that
She just she did it didn't say nothing about it
Then they went to go leave later and they fucking ran into this blood and shit on the front
This is pretty foul. I gotta say and you know the way that it was to it was like, you know how the you know
Fresh concrete nice gray, you know, it's a nice nice little place
So that shit was fucking that shit was on there like you could see it really clear you could tell what it was very gross people
He's like too misplaced.
And they want to judge other people too.
Exactly.
He just peed on the front porch and left a bloody pattern tampon.
Is that what it was?
Oh my god, that guy's beauty.
Yeah, she's a nasty one, dude.
I've seen her fucking scratch her pussy and sniff it.
She's nasty.
She's like a dude.
She does shit like a dude would do.
What is?
If I scratch my balls and sniff them, that's normal.
I'm a dude, but you're a lady.
That's fucking weird.
ladies don't do shit like that
well some ladies obviously do
that's not a lady that's a fucking
she thinks she's 19
I mean that's
I'm only there for the summer queue
never forget, never forget
four summers later
Four summers later the thing is that he treats her like shit
Four summers later now now he's followed her to another person's house
She was living there first and then he went out on his ass and she was like oh you can come live with me at somebody else's house
Yeah
She lot how the fuck you lose a seventy-five dollar apartment seventy-five dollar a month fucking section eight apartment
How the fuck do you lose 75 dollars a month? Yes? Yes?
This is all paper work to this is all this is all out with it an official paperwork that was shown on stream and everything
This is all his great. This is what this is what Sam Man's entire channel was built on was showing pebs paperwork
This is how this all started was because of pebs being a fucking abusive mother
So now we got fucking Sam idiot and and and these two doing this shit now
That's why this is all like the way that it is now because it's pebs and zea being fucking scumbags
And the reason why the third pass is coming up is because I haven't seen any of this and he just literally fucking
Alex, shut up Q. So Alex brought Zayn to this when we were talking brain and Q, right?
But he's mad at me and gamble. So he decided to bring this up. So now this is what's happening.
So people are like, no, they're streaming the past. No, it's not the past for me.
This is my first time ever seeing any of this because he decided to mention my name.
BSM says it was $72 a month and it went up to 350 years when she lost custody because
Roche's crawled out of her son's backpack then went up to seven.
That happened all that's right. That's real bro. It's crazy cuz when you talk about shit like that with the roaches calling out of the backpack
It seems fake. It seems like we just made shit. It's like, you know, Janet ate the dog type shit and fucking
It's real that really happened. It's really in the yes paperwork
When you take what we just watched and then you see that there may or may not have been a kid involved in any of this
It kind of makes it much darker
The thing that a kid would ever have to hear what we just heard on those videos
Did you ever
Did you ever see the clip of fucking Zaya whenever they had her son over to visit that that's apartment where we were just watching the map
So they listen to you. It's a lot worse. They had they this is years ago
Maybe two three years ago. They had her done over to the apartment
I need to see a brandy Q is crystal
They had her son over to the apartment and fucking played TTS
For him and the TTS is calling the kid a faggot and all this shit like saying crazy stuff to this kid and they just let it go
They use the kid for content literally put him in front of the camera knowing that people were gonna be saying crazy shit to the kid on on
TTS 100%
Check guys this Jenny the dog is so real to be
That was on Thanksgiving I almost forgot
That's awful
Thanksgiving on top of it. Yeah, he yeah her son went to visit them for Thanksgiving and what they do stick a camera on him and let the
TTS go nuts
These are vile vile people is what you're telling me. That is some real shit, too. Like this is all fucking
facts, dude
Well, Zea, when we started streaming he was saying some unkind things to you, Crystal.
But after we just heard you have to look at the source, like this is a vile person saying
these things.
No, he is.
Who gives a fuck what he says?
But the thing is, his life is a mess.
Karen and Alex dragged me into this shit with Brandon Q. Zeya and then this and fucking psyche
They're all don't worry about it. Just clown them. They're clowns. That's what we're telling you
So I don't know if you know this gamble, but someone actually made a youtube channel now
That says gamble loves kids like oh, so Brandon's trying to be like trying to project it like I might need to play
Brandy Q loves kids, but now he's not even streaming me. So now I know what to do. Oh, he's he's he's learning. He's learning
I'm gonna be
Yeah, these people are doing it to themselves yet. They want to protect. Oh, they're all liars
It's the internet blah blah blah like if you have to like go and protest outside
Like do you know that the cops are probably thinking okay more than likely than you're a fucked-up human being
Well, I think it's only fair who was putting the spotlight on Brandon being the sick piece of shit that he is and he definitely is
I think it's only fair that Zana gets the same treatment, which you know
Like they're doing anything currently they're the ones that are
Repeating shit and like getting triggered just because Gamble's name got brought up like the fuck
Gamble says a tad and they all freak out
Well, now Alex can't use a zea against me because now like watch she's gonna team up with zea next
I can promise you that
They are all on the same level like it's so weird
There who still defend zea
I
Appreciate you letting me up here. It was fun Q take care of yourself, buddy
Anyone who supports these predators, I'm gonna ban I did ban Sean phase. Can you hear?
Hello, hello. Can you hear me? Okay? No, I think I think RG was echoing
Okay, can you hear me though? His headphones probably died. Yeah, I can hear you. Okay. Okay. Okay. So anyways
And what is interesting is these people are so like?
Alex is the one that started the shit with Zaya Zaya though. You are
Something else like you're full in your 40s like that's
Just as bad as brain and Q the fact that you're defending brain and Q. Yes
I banned Sean phase out of my chat. Why because he's like, oh, what's putting going on because okay?
So let's bring up Sean phase Sean phase
You hit on Alice when she was like barely legal. Okay, so just I would recommend you just stay far away for me
Karen talked about a five-year-old penis, which was weird Alex
Likes these weirdos and goes back and forth. I don't know why like
I don't get it. And then it's clear as day, so Brighton abuses animals. Zea abuses his girlfriend.
Well, what the fuck?
Oh, Zea still has yet to formally
Say to my knowledge 20. Oh, okay. So it's Sean. Hey, Nicolette. I was talking
Zaya has yet to formally acknowledge pebs as his significant other to this day
Zaya for whatever reason and that's why I banned him
He's like man, why are you up laying? Why are y'all going to this day?
Zaya still won't say peps is my girlfriend. We all know it's true though. No
Wait a minute, is it on IRL new time news times hold on IRL news times. What you're dancing for Alex right now
I'm not dancing for Alex. I'm not dancing. This is what Alex wants you to do fucking talk about her
No, I just want to look at the pole. I are L news times
No, I ain't giving out our channel
Well, and I'm sorry that my my remote sometimes doesn't know what the fuck I'm talking about explain the stripper per stripper pole to her
You mean the stripper pole that fucking
When Alex took pictures of fucking
Control his kid and fucking stupor impose them on a stripper pole. Oh
I thought he was saying what he I thought he said pole not like pole
Um
Yeah, you ever hear about that crystal? No, I don't think so. This is just to preface this
This is maybe a year and a half two years ago. This is before you
Listen, this is before this is before you could use AI, right?
Alex was at her little one of her on her little wars with controller right now right now
For example, you heard the other day when Alex was like she's trying to protect control this kid and all this listen to this
At one point when Alex was mad at controller, she took pictures of her daughter and then like edited them on to a stripper pole and then put people from the community in the crowd like me and Zaya and a couple other people that lady is crazy.
Q because you're you keep going like like
We're gonna have I'm trying to have a conversation with you
But you're like too like worried about talking about Alex like if you want to talk about Alex just fucking
Isaiah you ding dong. Yeah, you go back and forth
They're all fucking weird
Learn how to have a conversation don't worry about the chat you're on a panel
Okay, you want to take over the stream for a little bit
Yeah, sure. What are you gonna go do order food?
Okay, I mean
I'm not gonna do it yet. You thought you're on stream to your 20 viewers. I'll be glad I'll have yeah
My 20 viewers just like fucking Victor de Leon the only difference is I have 200 subs and it was 26,000
No, I know I trust you. He handled it. Well, I showered one day
I know me and Kate sat up here and fucking we forgot we were even on your panel. I thought I was on Kate's panel
Sometimes I just want to leave my stream, you know, I was like hey Kate
Can you drop the link and she was like we're on crystals panels like oh, yeah
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know if anybody has heard this Karen long off song, but it's pretty funny
My friend bride made it
It's pretty catchy
It's pretty catchy, loving, I guess he's 66.
Only the letter Q.
If you type in only the letter Q, that's my channel, but I don't really go live.
I know I hate AI music too.
I like this song though.
Because AI music is the only part of AI that I don't want.
And my car.
When I sing to it, y'all will love it.
Because I love singing to this song.
I like this song, but this is on the check.
It's more crystal-leaves.
Does anybody wanna come up here
before she doesn't have the ability to let anybody up?
You better come up now.
This song is great.
I like this song.
If you're gonna come up, you better come up now
because she's gonna go for probably like 30 minutes.
Who?
You.
What about me?
I'm saying if somebody wants to come up here,
they better do it now before you leave.
I can leave you just said you just asked me to fucking take over your stream
Yeah, like I said you're gonna go order food
Yeah, I mean I can me out you ready for good. I'm not hungry right now for some reason I
Think I ate a big lunch. That's probably why don't you like minnows?
Huh
What like the candy? I don't know what does a blob fish eat?
What what is I didn't even know that was a real animal until you I
Never even heard of that thing until you
You want to make fun of you?
Sure, I look like a caveman. Oh, this is my little brother, right? And he's gay. He just won't does
Okay, he was okay. Wait a minute. Who was born with fetal alcohol syndrome
But he likes to you know portray that he was a crack baby, whatever right his mom is a crack. I know now
He exaggerated so he was born with fetal alcohol
Alcohol syndrome he got dropped on the head as a baby a few times
We have two different mothers
He's just jealous that my mom loves me and his mom abandoned him
And so sometimes I just really want to hit a door into his face my mom to be Korean
Well, I'm sorry. Can you show your face?
Well, hi, I know you're all every time I join your stream you're like, please show your
Yeah, just so that everyone knows how like I'm gonna start just just so everyone knows how fucking dashing and good-looking I am
We've already done this before I'm cute
So I was explaining to people that I had some bubbly farts and I did it like
Oh, and he still continued to talk about my asshole
Who?
You
Remember the other night talking about your ass. When was I talking about your asshole the other night?
And so then I decided to fart through the microphone on you and clumsy was up here. Remember or were you too drunk to remember?
I don't care about your asshole fuck your asshole
Don't understand why my little brother is trying to ask about my asshole like I get that maybe you take it up that way
I don't care about it problem. What let me alone. Oh
How much have you drink today?
Not really anything honestly, well, that's good. I'm not even screaming at you yet
And I kind of you have you have a little bit. Well, no, I had to yell because that one video was really loud
I wasn't trying to yell. I was trying to talk over the video
Anyway, so what is your choice of dinner tonight Vienna sausages?
No spam no, I spam no actually I had
I had I just took a I had a rotisserie chicken
I took a bunch of it and like chopped it all up
And then I mixed it in like some chicken rice that I had and I put cheese on it
And then I melted the cheese on it. I ate it. We don't say the n word here. So
Actually neighbor. Yeah
Anyhow, so Q um
Q's favorite store is a family dollar. I
Love me some family dollar
Yeah
Another thing he likes too is
Family dollar is the best dollar store like cuz you know, there's dollar general dollar tree and family dollar family dollars
The purple berry and it's so good if you make like fried rice and put spam in it. It's actually really good like no
I do that all the I actually do that and what some and what some kimchi inside
That's how Koreans do it. They do like their kimchi fried rice and they'll add like spam and it's really good
And I honestly I don't even cook this spam. I just you know
It's already cooked, but I don't heat the spam up
Like I just take this fan right off the can and put it in there
I don't give a fuck. I let the rice and the eggs eat the heat to spam up
So anyways, um cue there is a song I'd like to sing so you know as they were like in that stream
He was playing Eman, you know
Fuck you know, I want to do the Frankie version just because I like the part where she's like you're crying like a bitch
Talk I got neighbors on my mind
I got neighbors on my mind.
Getting that from YouTube.
Okay.
On my mind!
Slop on my knob.
Corn on the cob.
Get in with me and do your job.
This is not a prayer.
You shouldn't have started with me.
no no no yeah I don't know why you're crying like a bitch talking shit like
something I'm gonna ask you a predator
You're just like Brandon to cry in there. Fuck you right back. You are a pedo
Alright
Q I think they should now call you the songbird of our generation
My gosh, I want to almost maybe tear up with that performance
Because you want to hear me sing I sing all the time actually you just don't want to thank you
This is for you. Okay. Oh now you're dedicating songs to me. How sweet
Yeah
Because baby, I'm gonna do right. I
Mean it's better than crying man. So you gotta give that up, you know my playlist is better
No, it's tired of your broken promises problems like show your face and different numbers and numbers
And with your fellas your fellas
Getting jealous you jealous. I was what you when you didn't have no dollar in the dollars Q
See Q broke, right?
drama
Okay, please
Q show your face
Say it again
Q show your face again
No, jeep don't
Yeah, come on Q show your face. Let me just do some Britney Spears, okay
No, goodbye, Earl. Why do you always want to see my face?
Just go with it. It's funny, you know
I mean, I'm not sure I'm not a piece of me crystal
Okay, fine. Don't make nice
I'll sing this somebody really fuck this dime up
And you see me sing some blink 182 without help cue
Okay, so people tell me all the time to like just like like this like Karen wants me to forgive right?
I'm never gonna forgive her the people that want me to forgive them and like think that I'm gonna turn on gamble this
This is to y'all. I think Karen and Alex are two very well-adjusted sane individuals
She loved me two boys like trying to backpedal and it doesn't work just like you
Show face show face
No
Yeah, I always show face, but then when people start asking me to show face then I don't want to
Jimmy any Christmas
I'm not your monkey how buddy guy
Compadre amigo nigga
Oppositional Defiance.
Exactly, Quasimodo predicted this.
What happened to Crystal?
If we were talking we can't hear you.
Just to let you know
If you're talking we can't hear you
Little crystal
She's a blood fish in a big ocean
Like saying better than you shit. I'm basically like ursher the white ursher
Fuck that. I don't want to be the white usher. I want to be the white Nate dog.
I just want to chill and twist the land.
Good times in my seven forty five.
Crystal.
I want to ask you what your updated thoughts on
Attila Bach are, and how you feel about recent transpirings.
That's how you know she's not really there.
If she doesn't respond to that, that's how you know she's not there.
How do you feel about the dildo bag?
Yeah, no fuck that. I want to be the white Nate dog. I
Know I remember watching that back then the whole when when I remember being a viewer back then when the whole fucking
You know scheme ask Andy when and got the stole jewel in the till his shit out of crystals house
And I didn't really think about it the way that I think about it now that I'm like a bit older
I'm like damn that was literally like a home invasion fucking like I just thought of it as like content because at the time
When you're watching it, you don't know if it's scripted or what's going on or you know
You have no idea if it's real or if it's just some bullshit at the time
I didn't even think nothing of it. I just thought it was some goofy shit
But then you look back on it. You're like damn he literally did
deal with them shit. I'm here
Yes, I remember that gamble
Can you hear me
Crystal yeah, this is prayer
Crystal in remote. There it is. Okay. First of all, Q. Where did you go? Can you can you not hear me?
No, I can't hear. Oh
Hold on. Let me come back. I
Have an Android so it's probably her
I heard that this is an iPhone problem because I never have this problem with anybody and I have a galaxy
Hello
Hello. Oh, well, you're talking this whole time out there. You're ignoring me
No, I mean I was talking but I mean nobody could hear you either. Oh
That's great. So nobody heard me sing. That's great
Well, let's let's know we heard you know we heard you sing the first song. I don't know if you sung any other songs
Have another time. That's gonna be great. I'm gonna run for the weekend. I just took it like like friends
Some of the warp tour
Here we go vegan Patriot we just teenage dirt bag
This is brandy kill
This brings back
By the way, I like this song in 2011. Wait, by the way
Gamble Gamble says
Gamble says remember how Alex wanted to fuck Attila. No, Alex did fuck Attila. What do you mean? They lived together for like three months
She they live together for three months
If you think you think that remember
If you think that Alex would live with somebody like Attila who is a sex pest for three months, and they didn't have sex you're fucking crazy
Don't see gambles girl my fiance this was like one of the songs that me and him actually agreed on
Cause I'm just a teenager back, baby. Don't let me brand a cue. No, don't come after me brand a cue
Listen to I am made and maybe with me
Leave me alone you pedophile
Crystal look at the chat
Fact is his teenage dirt bagging and Brandon is probably gonna be rewatching this is gonna be hilarious
Look at the chat friends that dick
He bring up
Now he's simply kicked
Look at the chat. It's all my block
He doesn't know who I am Brandon sure doesn't know who I am and she yeah, I don't go fuck about him either
Look at the chat
Sir back, baby. I'm a few comments
Leave me alone you creep oh brandon
Look at Alex recent post
is talking magic is also a predator.
Yeah, but
Oh, I'm going after teenage dirt bags.
I'm just saying.
I don't know. Can you hear me?
Yes, I can fucking hear you.
Yeah, she's just really good at fucking ignoring people.
Go look at Alex recent post, idiot.
I don't.
You go look at it. You say I'm the one that's obsessed you ding dong. I can't fucking again. We'll told you to go look at it
Don't look at Alex post dickhead on IRL news times I don't know. She's got 16 channels pick one
I was enjoying that's viral news times. I are L news times
That or IP to wiki whichever one I
Don't know she jumps back and forth
Trying to figure out how to go to her channel. I can't leave my if I leave to go look at it
I'll leave the panel hold on
Shut up crystal. Let me see IP to wiki. I
Can't you want to talk this much? Maybe you should go live and start a stream yard
Well, I can't look at community posts on YouTube. So is she live? She's me
Hold on. Hold on
Somebody tell us what it says. How about that Barb? Can you do us a favor? Tell us what it says
Because now I'm interested if it was enough to get game board to come in here to tell you to look at it
Then it must be interesting. Okay. I'm reading get you ding dong. Okay
I just
Look you got gamble crashing out what's wrong with you shame on you
You're gonna make gamble go get back on the shit again
Dressing them out like this. Okay. I
Couldn't hear gamble. What did he say?
He said to he said to that the community post says that you are gambles puppet is what Alex said on the phone
Said you are gambles puppet
Can y'all hear me still? Yeah, they can hear you
Some reason if I can hear you they can hear you okay, okay, you can hear me
Yes, okay, so it says this 51 minutes ago
Considering everything known about pebs and everything known about crystal considering Zaya. I mean pray as established pattern
Who do you think is more of his type?
Every few years Zaya moves on to a new girlfriend
FYI today Gamble publicly made it clear that crystal is indeed Zaya's type and crystal does tend to act as gambles
puppet. He's controlled and manipulated her for years.
He's like, I'd say as to exactly how to pull
her strings as well.
Um, wait a minute. What you I didn't even talk to gamble for two years. How is he?
I know like prayer like how the fuck does gamble control me as a puppet?
I'm a 37 year old woman who lives on my own who pays my own bills
He's got a fiance. What are you on about you? You whack a doodle. He's a strong black independent woman
Leave Priscilla alone
Didn't we establish that I don't fuck with prayer
So why is she making a bit a short saying this that I hold on
Hold on
Thanks for getting that stupid fucking song stuck in my head
She said I'm willingly teaming up with someone who's a predator. Wait a minute. What what what are you kidding me?
Smokey you ain't smokey you telling the truth there she wait
She literally be like laying in her bed in the morning like hmm. What type of bullshit can I spin today?
This woman is wack like she was saying
Did she not listen to the current events that I don't fuck with Preya?
And that's why you know that she is a she's a fake tooth
And if and it flies out sometimes when she yells too much on camera it happened before you ever seen her fake
Tooth like I banned him from my chat
She's a ding bag like
Okay, so now she's targeting gamble like gamble manipulates me controls me what?
That's insane nobody controls me
I'm a teenager back, baby
I'm just a teenager back, baby.
Thanks for getting that song stuck in my head.
Why don't you leave me alone?
And you, Brandon Q, just need to leave the teens alone.
Stop calling him Brandon Q, just Brandon.
I'm Q, he is Brandon PDF.
I sing way better than you, Q.
Yeah, well, you're a girl.
But that's a guy's song and you just
You just sung in monotone Q
Yeah, that's how I sing monotone because I'm a real inward
so what can't like
These people are wackadoodles like for real
Like there's something deeply
Alexander's just bitter that she doesn't have a child that's really her main gripe in life
So she takes it out on everybody else. She said this many times
This is self-admitted from Alexander Mayer's if she's upset that she never found a husband and a kid never had
Was able to like make a family have a family so she takes it out on people on the internet
She's admitted this on her own and I feel like we need to replay how she has brain and q on her panel
On what the part that she thinks she goes after just Jen so hard because literally just Jen lives the life that alex wants to live
Ex porn star has a fucking happy family a child living their life doing their thing
That's why she hates Jen so much
I mean as much as beef that Trisha and just Jen have they both agree that
prayer
and
I'm braping
Well, I don't really know. I don't feel like he's really beat BQ
weirdo
They're both weird as fuck and so is pubs and
No, I just judged Cardi Lee. I'm not gonna I'm not gonna count on that like
Love Cardi Lee and I'm not gonna judge her, but I don't know what the hell she was thinking
She says she's like this Christian lady, right and her faith your faith led you to petto's do like an animal abusers and
like
The fact that she's still pushing this narrative is
wild
Who Alex Alex? Oh?
But pray it was to get mad at me for what Alex is doing. Who's bringing him up again?
Alex no crystal crystal pray a
Alex crystal that I have to explain something to you. Isaiah doesn't it's not that he
It's not even that he gets mad. He loves the attention of anybody who's talking about him
Especially somebody who's getting the traction and the viewers that you do he loves that shit. That's what he thrives off of
He doesn't he doesn't get mad or care either way
He just likes the attention whether it's you're saying whether you're telling you him that you love him
And you love his streams or you're calling him a PDF either way to him. He likes it
That's why so many people including gamble himself
Realized at a certain point that he enjoys the attention more than he hates the negativity of being called a PDF
So it's not even worth going at him, but you know what music is Marty went through the same thing
Okay, but you never stop talking. I don't hear you. Why are you afraid of Alex like every time we talk about her?
You like go off and talk about something me. I'm afraid of Alex
Yeah, the same person who I was just on a panel with her screaming about how gay her dad is and calling her the n-word. Yeah, I'm so
Okay, well cute. That makes me look really bad. Thank you very much. That just makes it worse for me
But whatever everybody knows. I'm crazy. It ain't no surprise. Okay, so chunky
I mean, that's what Preya likes to call you. Why is he mad at me again when Alex keeps bringing him up?
And he keeps coming at me. I just happened to see the clips and clips did not do him any justice
I mean, we all heard him say, Chunky, you know what I mean, Chunky?
The dude was screaming.
Oh yeah, Chunk is cool, but he likes to play both sides.
I didn't start it with Zaya.
Alex started the shit.
Alex drugged me and gambled into it when we were only going about Brandon Q.
But now that Preya wants to defend Brandon Q.
Which Brandon Q allows me.
You know Chung's North Korean, right?
That's why he's like that. He was adopted from North Korea. Stop it. So he is like a race is kind of a spy
He's like a spy
We either put some re SPC TMI stream. He's a North Korean spy. Oh
My god, you're so dumb
Anywho I'm was trying to ask for him for his thoughts so Chung E we had a
Put these clips up, right? Well, I didn't do anything actually. It was other people, you know
That's like my first time watching clips and stuff. I mean
Well, your little friend decided to go at me for what Alex did Alex brought him up
Alex made crazy allegations against me like I support certain shit I said I
don't I think Brandon Q's a fucking weirdo Karen brought me into the shit with
Brandon Q well Brandon Q was already stalking me but then again it all the
common denominator is Alex Myers he's racist right and then now I'm very very
aware of Preya
So why is prayer mad at me?
Because of stuff that I wasn't even around for is being shown on my life because Alex wants to have beef with me
looping
Make it make sense. I
Looping prayer because I don't really know him like that if it wasn't for Alex making him relevant
You're looping inward
At least you didn't say it you just said inward, but whatever
Yeah, cuz I actually like you
Trunk on his thoughts, okay
Well, I'm gonna get
No, no he won't Chung goes anywhere Chung goes all chat
I like mr. Chung but the fact that prayer things don't mean Chung you're so close like Chung
He's probably watching you like ain't watching you pray
Chung Chung is the type of motherfucker. He just goes around and he likes to he likes to see the content
You know, he just likes to see the content that you know
He likes to see people go out war and have fun and talk shit
I'm wrong with it. Whatever
Chung is one of the only other people from ETC that I don't mind
A couple of them. I don't mind. He's one of them cute. Can I just say this song is the reason why I feel this way right now because of you
This is now. It's my fault. I want to be in love
What
So, what are you talking about? I'm trying to refer this song
To me this is like a pads and pray I like breakup song right here
No, this is a mind and cue break up song actually, okay now you need to relax
Get they were together all that time. He was taken up for granted apparently I
Can't deal with stroke off. I really can't he's so annoying
She's looking for he caused her up. That's cute tripping on the phone now keeps working out
Okay, fine talk I
Just get bored talking about the same like merry-go-round like weirdos and a lady's like
I can't believe you're the one saying that to me you've been going on a merry-go-round about weirdos for three hours now crystal
Not come on. We've been all we've met me and other people in the chap and telling you to move on and you don't want to move on
My little brother is a little slow Jiminy Christmas
I'm like in the zone. I'm in the music zone right now. I just want to have fun
Even ginger tired of your ass
Ginger can you leave the plastic bag alone? I don't know why cats are obsessed with fucking plastic bag
What is it ginger? My cat. No, that's my cat doing plastic stuff. What?
Yeah, I'm so tired of these people these people really killed my brain
So handsome ginger
Can we have respect to this handsome prince
Not even I that's the sad thing. It's just like I like this song too this song girls and boys girls like
Yeah, this is
Educated you might want to drink you he's well dressed not funny. That's cute
Most conversations he fit all situations
For everything
Girls don't like boys girls like cuz in my name not predators like Brandon
Handsome boy. Can you stop fucking up my comforter, please?
Fun day. Who's not fun day?
Paper or plastic cues obsession right now
Habits the cat
Stop things freeze
Hey
Okay, Q can we talk what do you want to talk about Q?
What are your thoughts on the ongoing conflict between Afghanistan and Pakistan?
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
I gotta go to Brandon Keele's kids.
Here we go.
It didn't take long.
Because I'm listening to Gamble, who allegedly I'm a puppet for, you know?
According to Alex.
Did I hit the right one open his live go to get go to Brandon's live right now?
Oh, we have to go we have to listen to that creep again. That's what that's what
Much rather okay fine. Hold on. I mean it must be interesting must be interesting
Must be something going on
Oh an old clip of mine about Trisha I did throw up at her house three times
Out of migraine big boys. Do you do me and Trisha made up? She still will choose me
Wait, he's saying I'm a lesson Trisha's dog. That's gross. Never did I do that?
Well, no, obviously everybody knows you didn't but it's just it's just to say his mind is that sick that he just thinks about shit like that
Like everybody knows that that's like never like that's not even ever been a thing in anybody's mind. Like nobody's ever been
Puppet master reporting no crystal
What happened was if you go back maybe like three or four minutes and hear it
He's watching clips of you and he's really drunk and he says he goes. I think that
Crystal molested Trisha's daughter
what forgive me for laughing and it's just so insane like yeah right it's like it's like
so insane you can't help but laugh but it's well because it's his pathology it's if anybody doesn't
like him he immediately calls him a pedophile and i said this was gonna happen a few days ago
that like eventually he's gonna start calling crystal a pedophile too apparently you molested
trish's daughter so i you could go back like four minutes listen to that and then you know you
What's true, and then you know it gives you something to do you can keep singing teenage nerf bag
I don't know. I'm just trying to help
Are you okay? Okay
So how weird that I can't cross this so the ones that are the weird narrative
This is the chick here the weird fucking weird-ass creep bitch that's associated with Dan won
She's flexing that
Trish was out of it or she was fucking off doing whatever and she and I'm 37
I was like 34 at the time. I'm an adult wait let the clip play with the clip player in like a
domination sort of way like
Access to her daughter and shit, dude
That's why are you obsessed with her daughter?
But you trying to like put it on me remind you I'm an adult. Okay, you know, there was one time
I was watching a Trisha Lisha stream one time
I was watching a Trisha Lisha stream and I saw Brandon Q go into her chat and say that he wanted to be the stepfather
By the way, this is so old. Wait, is this after that or is this or was I on the right spot? Don't worry about that crystal
Don't worry about that. We know we all know this is old
No, you are
I don't obsess over her daughter like you do you weirdo leave her alone you psycho
Don't let them get you caught up having to like explain yourself about old shit. We all know this is old
She went to go to the store you ding-dong cuz she's an adult and I'm an adult. What the fuck?
Yeah, me and Trisha said shit about each other who fucking who but at the end of the day
What
Why are you bringing up her daughter you sick?
The thing is is that Brandon's talking about things that he wasn't even like around for he wasn't even thought of back there
I'm not the one that brings up her daughter
Brandon wasn't even a streamer
He wasn't he didn't even know about any of these communities back when all this shit happens
So like for him to act like he knows about anything is crazy
I don't have crystal is I don't know what's going on with crystalline. I think I think she needs help
Crystal do you need help wait, okay? Can you hear me now?
Hello, oh, yeah, like Verizon can you hear me now? Yeah, where was anybody able to hear me?
Well, that's what I was saying. Oh, well when I was talking I was all like why is he even bringing up our daughter?
That's weird. She went to us the store. I'm an adult like hello
I'm not no creep Trisha would never allow a creep around her daughter you weirdo and me and her
What this was when me and her at beef?
I probably shouldn't have even brought up her daughter when we had beef or say anything because Trisha really is a good mom
And I know and I would never want to harm her or anything, but Brandon Q
Why are you bringing up her daughter? You're the predator not me. It's you you sicko
You couldn't even be why are you even like giving?
any of that like because don't you know we all know we know we know you're not a predator crystal
if anybody thought you were a predator it would be a lot worse for you right now on youtube no
shit it wouldn't be this fun the thing is i'm a woman
i'm not obsessing over people like sexually don't do don't play the controller card
i'm a girl i'm just kidding i'm just fucking with you i never did weird
shit with the reborns that he fantasizes about i i don't understand another female bro and
Okay, and if that was true, then why did nobody call me out back then? Oh, because it wasn't true
Like to me, but I don't I'm not even mad because I know it's no this is a good thing you need to use these people for content
it's a great thing use Gaia and fucking and
Brandon diddler here for content. Fuck them. Talk shit. I mean
Crystal this is what the people are here for I mean come on people are here
They want to see you fucking you know do your thing chicken wing not 24-7. I'm not saying go on 24-7 spurge breeze
But people love this shit
After you said it in my chat, I really don't give a fuck because I know I'm not like, oh, what the fuck?
This is hilarious.
So now on the PDF, which Gable already said a few days ago, that's the clip he's playing now.
What's true is that you can give me something to do.
You can keep saying teenage fair fact.
I don't know.
I'm just trying to help him.
You just didn't say that she was taking care of her baby, right?
Oh yeah, they were up.
I was saying, what the fuck is wrong with you?
Okay, let's go to Brandon Q loves kids since he's restreaming me.
Brandon Q loves kids.
And remember when Brandon Q and his little his little girlfriend said remember when you said you were gonna
Put a baby in me so that whenever it was born you could fuck it never forget
Never forget how wild that is and nobody brings that up. Why does nobody ever bring that up?
It's in this clip
Yes, you do you said you she's cute and you don't care how old she is and you're 30 something years old
Okay, you want to restream me bitch? Oh, you'll okay people will see the truth that you're a pedophile
What the hell?
No, I'm not recording you.
I'm not recording you.
Well, I don't give a fuck about that talk
A 14 year old girlfriend?
Oh, you're...
Oh, this is when he says monkeys
Can soul
Oh
Dude everyone's triggered by me. I was just trying to okay
Okay, can I just say this everybody is so triggered by me and honestly
What's funny is I just wanted to listen to songs and they want to ruin my piece. Okay, Alex is talking about me now
IRL news times
Let's listen to this little fucking Negro might
Is she on our old news times talking about me or?
Doast she can't do anything when you play the audio to your TV. That's like that's a golden method
I don't know what channel she's live on. No, I know I was there's only two of them
I wrote news time or IP to wiki
Hey, let me rewind this. Okay. This is a perfect strategy crystal. Yeah, because then brainy Q is restraining me, right?
Because no not only that because if you were Alex and then if you were to play if you were to play Alex's stream like like through
The stream yard like you do with videos when Gamble comes up
She'll strike you for that but when you play through the TV like this you can hear what she's saying and she can't strike you
It's perfect
Right because it's not she can't copyright her content this way. It's impossible
No, because it's on the big screen.
Mm-hmm. She can't copyright that. She could try what she wants.
Everyone can listen.
With another update in regards to um...
Say my name, say my name, when no one is around you.
Since um, a few years ago.
She's obsessed with me.
That I decided to redefine the situation revolving around Big Trolla and her minor age daughter.
Oh, wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Duh.
Say, I never said that was okay.
But I did it like the way she went at...
Rick's child who has cancer, you ding-dong.
called RumoredHeadow.com
But ever since I redefined what is actually
the legal
perspective of what's going on with Big Troll of
Zaya and her minor-aged daughter
Someone from a few years ago has taken a lot of interest in
My live streams and I was questioning as to why I think I have
come to the conclusion
The person I'm referring to is someone as Chris. Oh gamble
gamble would you like to come up here and listen to this?
So, yeah, literally when he
Fucking computer
This computer and it's playing on his shit right now. No shit. I can read
But she just mentioned Gamble, so I was asking if Gamble wants to come up to respond, you ding-dong queue.
No, fuck you crystal. I love you Q. I love you too, Crystal. Thanks
You're just annoying
There are you the call I know when I know that's why people watch you. I know
For the first and only time at her home. She did indeed invite me to her home and we're gonna talk
Okay, no, I didn't invite you you were already on the way to my house. What was I supposed to do?
I was in shock
You should have started across out in the front yard. That would have got her away a
Problem with lying. Oh lying. She's an insistent liar
You mean you she's lied for years that she did not invite me to her home
But I have shown the receipts and we're gonna look at those again today
But I'm thinking that it's okay. I wish the phone call beforehand was recorded where I told you I was gonna have plans
And you're like a little too bad
Like, can you play that phone call, please?
I'd love if you had that phone call.
So manipulate, narcissistic, you racist,
you have zero credibility, you let a pedophile
on your fucking panel, but carry on lying about me,
by saying, I'm a liar, Gamble's a liar,
everybody's a liar but you.
That Gamble didn't know that Crystal did indeed.
We need a lyncher.
Issa's gamble may not know until jucex. There's a very high likely
Who is my e-mom? Oh, you mean? Oh, yeah, Alex once called me her e-son
That's why he's saying that she said that I was her
No, yeah, because Alex said that that me and good times were her e-father or she said that me and good
Alex and good times were my a parents is what she said
When she's older than you by no, no, no, no, no, no, no listen. She she said that her and good times were my a parents
I know it. She just says the craziest shit
I'm surprised you remembered that I forgot
Let's go ahead and take a look at the puppy master
It's like one month. She calls me at one month. She'll call me here. Eson the next month. She calls me a racist pedophile
It's just like back and forth back and forth
have five votes. Hopefully it has more now. Oh, five votes, five votes. Karen, Brandon,
Psyche, probably yourself, Alex, on all your fucking. Wait, wait, wait, so you're, you're
watching Alex's stream right now, right? Yes, Ding Dong. How many people are in the chat?
But here's the poll question of the day.
None, right? There's probably none.
And that is not my friend either.
People don't even type in her chat. It's crazy. They just watch her from a distance like a crazy person.
Today, Gamble publicly made it clear that crystal is indeed Zana's type.
And crystal gamble you got all this time to type in chat. Why don't you get your punk ass up here before I gotta start talking shit?
for years
He could easily guide sale as to exactly cooking and making content
But gamble wants to sit in the fucking in the chat get your ass up here again
I'm gonna start calling you by your first name
Um, I don't know exactly yes. Yes. I don't anyone care about this Super Bowl
I would never touch pray with the 10-foot ball you ding dong
But I do have some clips that I would like to share in regards to
Some developments when it comes to the situation revolving around gamble my god
Brandon Q
Irminger
Yeah, oh was she created to be a game changer sort of event
when it comes to the world of
IRL
We were still living in a pre Ronald Ray or a pre Jimmy Carter era
People like Alex would be locked up in a mental ward
Jimmy Carter passed legislation to allow people like Alexander to roam free
Shut up you we're listening to this. You know that you're talking about gambles shut up
Issues definitely are applicable
To the umbles resurgence now here's what I found comical about the situation
One of the key players in the situation is they are right. And as we all know, they are like
Can't believe gambles 32, holy shit comic books, right?
But guess who likes to equate themselves to Batman and has for not just his reappearance
He's obsessed with gamble
You're the one who keeps telling me to shut up because Alex is talking about him. You're obsessed motherfucker
No, because I'm reading my music to play recent time. I'm reading. It's cat fucked hard. Oh
Okay
He said I'm 32 and I have hair. I said I can't believe he's 32
Time has passed very fast
Watching that I've known about that nigga since 2018
To this clip didn't know here
I want to go back to a clip from April 30th
2026 I actually in previous videos
Misleabelled this clip as April 3rd notes from April. You're almost the same age as Batman
I agree with that lady whoever that lady is I agree with her, but he's not cool as fuck no more
Okay, so you all heard that that was just April 30th about seven days ago
That you hear that you hear crystal and not to be confused with crystal Marie
There's a lot of crystal. Yeah, we know the difference between dolphin teeth and the Queen
But crystal man said that she didn't give a f you see okay
Oh
Sorry
We already know Alex you're trying to spin your fucking shit Alex
We already know Alex everybody in this community is well aware of how much of a fucking bullshit or you are and nobody takes you serious
Imagine dedicating all of your fucking life and all of your time to recap in these communities and nobody around here takes you seriously at all
A long-term relationship.
You lost your credibility years ago, fuckhead.
I'm gonna give a man a chance.
I'm gonna lead to marriage, not at the least,
even though it may have been once upon a time.
But they definitely have had quite the interaction for several years
to my knowledge
gamble
lives his life as a straight heteroman he
Does seem to have a girlfriend. That's what they're doing. She's gonna be called gamble gay
The rumor is that Crystal as well is taken in her relationship, even though she does spend a vast amount of time on these YouTube streets, but then again, that does seem to be the pattern of a lot of...
I'm retired, I can do whatever the fuck I want.
fulfilling relationships that in actuality they are not who matriculate these youtube streets
but um gamble and chris philander basically defying dx back up i think it's time i mean
knew about zayna because i wasn't around for this day as shit are you dense bitch
it's time to fire dx back up a few days ago
That gamble would not DX is needed now more than ever
Zaya to Crystal and there's no way that you would not have spoken at great length
I'm serious gamble. You think I'm fucking around when has DX need been needed more than now
How many pedophiles are out here just fucking streaming free?
Come on, dude
So let's take a listen to this clip. I'll provide my commentary as I see fit
Well, yeah, you aged about other people, but some motherfuckers were always there
Don't forget motherfucker, but it may the force be with you and word
So there you go, you're here and say it and I'll rewind it just so that all of you can hear it clearly made six
on this clip wait a minute today is May 6 why are you filming a clip from a few
days there I was like hello hello his final two targets along with his band
Mary wine mommies known as DX were two people these days I feel more like Ben
And I could be wrong but I'm most likely correct
Brandon, I'm sorry it's hard for me to even distinguish between Brandon and
Gamble at times because they're both 34 they both have a similar look
I think they even have similar hair. See fascinating over gamble who that
Why mommy they're DX no why mommy's aren't DX, but there are a lot of wine mommies that were in DX
No, it's like, you know, not all Trump supporters are racist, but all people that are racist are Trump supporters
It's kind of the same thing with wine mommies and DX
You shut up
I'm trying to hear. It's like really on low. Oh my god. Let's listen to the retarded black woman babble about the same shit
Hold on. She's playing a clip you ding dong. Stop. You're ruining the content
And here we go
This was today, yeah
Well, why is it so crazy that um either Brandon or say it would have
Crystal's address, especially Zaya, considering that Zaya does like to visit the female live streamers from time to time, whether they like it or not, out on International Drive in Orlando, Florida, casually live streaming, and who approached me without my consent, Zaya.
You know that's totally Alex just just admitted that she is an accomplice
If I was to be unalive or these weirders come to my house. So she just admitted it
I love how Alex likes to spin shit though
Like I should like she forgets that we all or she doesn't she forgets that we all watch the fucking stream
Karen trying to hire Brandon Q as a hitman. Let's just take that out of their equation
Alex really wants one of these predators to come to my house to unalive me or to gamble's house
so
And let them both talk about Trisha's kid who she turned on I
Know look G G six. I already told crystal that she's giving Alex what she wants. She doesn't care
So I'll just let her do what she's gonna do
That's exactly what Alex wants
You know that Alex knows that Brandon Q's a pedophile?
She's just doing this for attention so Alex so you started all of this shit to put what me and Gamble in danger
Okay
Oh and Trisha
Because I've never even talked about him until you put me in the mix of it you ding don't
But the content content of
Inviting people to her home
But then lying publicly
and claiming that people show up uninvited.
Not just lying publicly about it, but how?
You did show up uninvited.
I didn't want you at my house.
I didn't want to ski at my house.
All right, because people warned me about skiing
and it scared me and you did it anyways
because you had an obsession with skiing, not me.
History of lying allegedly to gamble about it.
It's a law enforcement about it.
You know, this is interesting.
Let's keep going.
You have to know that I have a good spot.
Yeah, chicken cakes, did you fucking skip your medication yesterday, or are you just
like cool with like, like the shit that you were saying was
We're trying to hear don't muting me fucking
Already invited
No
No, that's weirdo behavior. I don't want anybody at my home you ding dog
Yeah, people say things
I teamed up with gamble
That doesn't mean we have to meet
That is quite odd chicken cakes, but whatever that shit was crazy. I couldn't believe this shit that was coming out of her mouth
Not anymore
Why is she bringing the past back up like I don't like him. Here we are
Here we are and I suggest that all of you take a look at this video. It's some post it on the
IRL news time channel
Okay, I start
The receipts with in addition crystal-stated I Alex on Jermayers came to her home uninvited as you can see in the following screen
But you won't play the call
Because after you said too bad. I'm already on the way there. Did I have a choice Alex? Did I really have a choice?
That's funny just Jen you mentioned that because chicken cakes thought that Alex was her friend for like a year
And then she got flipped on instantly. What a fucking idiot
Caroline cakes
Yes, it's called
Second, I think that's your second amendment rights. Yeah, I live in a state where we can have
Where there's gun laws
Now a chicken case you need spit on I think so if someone's wants to try to break into my house I can actually
Use deadly force
Trisha said the same thing when it came to Brandy Q, but when
My dogs today it's May 6 right he was Chris the land my dogs what you were gone for so long
You missed out on that to somebody in the chat just reminded me there was a stream that Alex had where
You know, they're okay, so let's for example at 6 p.m. She's in the chat and she's
Or she's not in the chat she's streaming and she's acknowledging her chat saying like oh look my nephew is watching
That's my nephew like shouting at her nephew blah blah blah blah and hour later
She was stripping naked on her stream
That's creepy and the only reason why she didn't get banned and I'm being I'm not being racist
I'm being her first house the room was dark and like had a purple light and she's black
And you couldn't really see any details, but she was 100% naked. She took all of her fucking clothes off and stripped
Do you remember that, just Jen?
I never...
Then why was...
Why was Preya asking me for my
Docs earlier?
Because I never gave my Docs out.
Gamble doesn't...
He was asking for all
information about Crystal Land.
He said, I want every piece of
He was calling out for all of it.
Yes.
Alex, again,
putting my life in danger.
But even here's the thing, the thing is, it's as long as you have-
Chickencake supports a groomer, it's okay.
You know, that's her, that, you know.
She wants to commit social suicide on the internet, that's her prerogative, not mine.
Like, pretty dry.
The way she's trying to manipulate the game is crazy.
Oh
And let me just say this okay, she edited it out and she put me
Erin didn't love my korean ice racist
Right
I didn't put that up on my stream. I don't even know how they were able to do that like that some oh
It's bad photoshop. You can see the blurry lines and stuff here where he has like a solid, you know ring
You could tell this is photoshopped, right? Yeah
Okay, anyways just pointing out her lies
Wow, so it sounds like there's two people on the same panel planning
To protect ourselves situation to where they can justify only
Oh, that's not true
Is self-defense what if the police came over and this guy is armed braining cue is an armed man like hello
Pay people to harm me and I won't let it happen
And Brandon Q said on his stream, he was going to go over to Bruno with the zeros house and go over they like what the fuck is wrong with you bitch like what is wrong with you you're weird.
The idea of harming Brandon Q makes me like grind my teeth because I want it so bad like I would love.
I would love to do some really evil grimy shit to him medieval style you know where they were they were like fray people alive.
Oh my god.
Like it just it makes my my voice like tremble cuz I just I would love to get my hands on that motherfucker
Oh my god, I would do unspeakable things
You brought up Cardi Lee a few days ago not us what the this is projection to the max. Oh my gosh who brought up the Cardi Lee
Mean Gamble didn't even once bring her up. It was Alex Alex did this. Why is she doing this daily on?
You can learn about him on rumor petto.com. He's staying with his girlfriend in the home of
A woman known as Cardi Lee. She's housing them feeding them
All kinds of good stuff
But what's interesting, and this is what I was talking about yesterday
You can find the live or the link to it in the description of this life
And my bad sweet Bruno with a zero was the one that out of that
Is that once upon a time?
Cardi Lee
Was a heavy supporter and donator to gamble you would go again
Since gamble is not a lot of comment over over there he can come up here and say
Gamble's not up here anymore
Yes, he is
Okay, I'll kick you. I'll kick you. I'll kick you. I'll kick you
Hello, but you go real life too, Crystal. I mean when I really think about it saying and Crystal are
quite the math
What?
What when I make on real life on someone
Years ago with gamble you think that's the craziest part about what she just said. She said that you and him are a match
I know that's weird too. Let me get there. That's the weird the worst part
My brain is slowly breaking everything down, okay?
What I'm taking in my real life. I don't want that man. He's prayer like grows
They both crave the online cloud. No, he craves miners
They both like to bully others maliciously and I'm just again offer cloud and attention
They're both past their prime
Nobody on this platform has made oh wait. I'm past my prime. I'm 37. I haven't even hit 40 with
Nobody on this platform has ever made more content concerning other people's minor-aged children than Alex has by far
So Alex is obsessed with children other people's children
Crystal is a homeowner, so that's perfect
So you're trying to invite this lunatic to my house? What the hell I
Think we need to get the police involved
They already are
And the SWAT team
Maybe I heard there's a hostage situation going on at Alex. No, that predator
No predators or nobody from the internet is allowed to my home except for Q45
Gamble and his fiance could come
Wait, you did the way you said that was really sounded really bad
How you said
No predators are allowed at my house besides Q45.
Well, okay. So I went from no predators are allowed at my house into the sentence.
But that is Q45.
The way that you said it sounded bad, that's all I said.
Okay. I'm sorry. Okay.
Then I said no people from the internet are allowed at my house, right?
Then I said except for Q,
the only internet people that can come to my house is Bar,
Oh, um, and, um, Tricia could come if she wanted to.
Justine?
How about...
Is, uh, is BrennanQ invited?
Oh, and Brennan with a zero, because that's my bestie online.
Can we...
Can we invite BrennanQ so I can skin him alive?
No, because he's a predator, and he's put a...
No, no, no.
We'll cook him over the fire.
And I'll tell you, Crystal is his type, even physically.
She's very diminutive.
She's about the height of a dwarf.
Diminutive, what does that mean?
I never heard that word before.
Wait, I'm a height of a dwarf.
I'm five, two, five, three.
What does diminutive mean?
I don't know.
Somebody in the chat helped me.
What does diminutive mean?
I've never heard that word before.
You know, like a petulant child.
and we know Zaya likes them.
Oh, a petulant child.
Wait a minute, did she just refer to me as a child
and once this predator at my house, huh?
What?
Hey, there's one thing,
there's a lot of things you can call me woman.
You can never call me short.
So that could work out,
and maybe that could work out.
I'm taller than your husband.
Conclusion of, maybe Cardi has also.
Maybe Zaya's come to the conclusion of it.
Maybe Chris fool.
Has reached this conclusion, but no only a weirdo would reach to this conclusion
My heart says get a restraining order on all you weirdos
These are all the weirdos and dorsas sit around and cry about control all day. I need an RO on Alex
She's the problem
Yeah, I think you're right
The problem is they run with that
Another thing why is she trying to match me with child predators like hello?
And why is she pimping me out? That's crystal
Crystal you're playing everybody. You're the ultimate chess master. You can't get a RO on her
I don't think it's possible
She's a drifter she goes from state to state Airbnb to Airbnb she doesn't live in one place
How can you get an RO on somebody that doesn't have a permanent address she's talking she's talking about shit on gamble
Let's keep going
Ginger can you calm down, please relax tranquilo ginger tranquilo
Where have I threatened anyone where
Wait, we all know you haven't threatened anybody we all know don't let her wind you up just laughing her
He's a clown
Four or five years ago now
She was very jealous of me upon meeting me and then she claimed that she wanted to break my fingers
And beat me up. When did I say that?
Years ago. No, you know crystal you did want to beat her up. I did one point because she threatened my life
I was just kidding. I didn't know nothing about that shut your mouth
Wait, she says she's never threatened me
Yeah, you are you're being around pedophiles, which is a threat to my life
You're trying to like go and find my dogs and give it to these people
Everybody knows your Docs crystal you're one of the most well documented people out there
Your Docs isn't nothing special if anybody wanted to do something with your Docs they would have done it by now
No, I haven't done anything wrong
Well, your job you have gamble on your panel. You're good. Okay? Nothing's gonna happen
The the the old the old op is is now your friend
Yeah, I know but it's whatever I she doesn't want to get involved this far
You used to be better at what you're doing right now because
People weren't as aware of your pattern
People oh my god, you know, let's rewind a little bit
This is totally I can't believe this woman takes herself seriously. I can't believe it
She she's she's either a really good actor or she actually takes herself seriously. I don't know which one's worse
Who was employing you DX that was not an established corporation at least not to my knowledge
Was it ever an LLC? Maybe it was I know you have merchandise
No, it was the Wyoming something
It's a Wyoming company or something only only real OGs know about the the Wyoming company
There's something like that the Wyoming something Wyoming corporation
Only real OG fucking take in full viewers know about the
It was the Wyoming something I care
But the problem is that you received donations in other words you profit it off of what you were doing
Which is what led you to being corrupt, which is what you are. So Wyoming or Wisconsin were manipulating crystalline
It's not just wrong, but it's evil again. He's not manipulating me you ding dong
If I can see through you
Others can see through you
Like I said you peaked
When you were younger
Which is a tragic thing for men like you
Because you get away with certain things when you're young, but then when you get old
You're not a novelty anymore. Who are you? I know you I know you're a new alt of somebody else
My question to you gambles. Why are you?
Raising the octave of your voice to try to sound younger when you're younger your voice was actually deeper
That means your voice at least an octave when it comes to that's the Lonnie
Good fuck
I was watching gamble when he was like 23 years old. He definitely isn't any doesn't seem any younger than he was now like
Not 23 maybe maybe 25 25 26 that was 21 22 at the time. I don't know gamble. She's on one
And here we are using. Okay, so he goes. Oh wait wait wait wait wait. Okay. You don't sound that much different
Let's me let me read this gamble appears to have made a deal with Zaya and my
pay grade being troll us situation involving
Fear her minor age
And in her what?
Gamble appears to have made a deal with Zaya and my coverage
Everybody knows that's bullshit everybody
My coverage on big troll us situation
What she's trying to do is she's trying to get Gamble to talk about...
Troll everybody knows that daughter, but that's what Alex is doing and gamble don't give a fuck about control and her kids like neither
Do I what everybody?
Well, no gamble. I still maintain and I mean you have gone when you join my panel before we used to go back and forth about this gamble
Back then you were fatter used to be a chubby little bastard. I don't care what you say
You were a chubby little bastard now you're in shape
You deny that all the time though
blame alex alex you caused all this shit nobody was talking about zay it was you and then now
he used to be like chubby and greasy back back in the uh when i when i used to stream on youtube
gamble was a chubby little greasy bastard it came a long way but it's okay it's i was almost 10 years
An American woman, very easy to villainize, and you know that very well, Gamble, you claim not to be a racist, you're one of the worst.
What?
Ooh, you're one of the worst, you're one of the worst.
No, Gamble, no, no, Gamble, stop it, I remember you being chubby as fuck, you look good now, back then you look like a hot mess.
Should be
You're the what what out of your fucking polo shirts better stop it
This is before I'm talking about before game will even
Listen to the video cube figure it out
Go fuck yourself
Go get hit by a door
Only if you're swinging it
Okay, I am
involving her minor age daughter did indeed interfere because how are you
going to be a PDF hunter if you're not going to actually hunt the PDF who's
after a nine-year-old little girl. Gamble's autistic and he has a food thing
where you only eat certain foods.
I'm just gonna get lost.
Gamble was a lovely little bastard.
I'll never forget it.
You can't erase my memories.
Okay, can I just say this?
Anybody who writes paragraphs like this,
like Alex, is mentally ill.
Okay, if you have to write paragraphs like this
of like a book, like Stella Rose,
you are mentally ill.
You are mentally ill.
I've definitely aged out.
This woman is a black job
Really have a picture of my head when game we used to stream on a little platform thing in the middle of the living room or whatever
It was like I had a little step up to it
It was like a little island step-up thing
It's a group
Such a weirdo
From being an alleged PDF hunter and I do want to make it clear
No, he's not
People donate him because nobody he has it. Where are you? She is a loony toon loony toon loony toon
No idea what I'm not talking about an island or a kitchen. It was like I remember there was a view you streamed in a place
Where you had to like to take a step up to get into it like you there was like a stair thing like
Q shot
You know what crystal? I'm speaking
Okay, so it's so is ginger
She's slandering gamble right now
and for quote-unquote entertainment.
And this particular timeline can be found on the post tab and there's links verifying-
I had a stare, I swear, dude. Fuck.
This is like back when you used to spam fucking Isis chat with DX shit like that long ago
Before Aaron Carter before all this
Who's being highly focused upon and possibly just I didn't even know gamble
I still I know well. Yeah, cuz you motherfuckers
One day I only know about him because this was like ice is fucking like boogeyman at a certain time when I used to watch ice
Beside and they'd be like, oh, you can't talk about gamble. Nobody mentioned gamble or DX
That's the only reason why I ever heard about him
The level of hypocrisy I've noticed, child abuse I've noticed, along with my having noticed the pattern of parents within the live streaming community accepting funds.
Because why does everybody think that I'm I'm crazy for saying that crack rock Chris was a diddler you all hear the purpose
Well, they were coming but because that's such a crazy thing to say or like am I talking about the wrong person?
Was crack rock Chris not a weirdo or am I just like am I just imagining shit
Like what the fuck
Every time I say fuck crack rock Chris. He's a diddler in a chat people are all like no we love crack rock Chris
We never did nothing
Yes, you did you brought our names up
With that sub, yes you did. Oh my god, is she delusional?
Gamble privately.
And I've decided that it's not in my interest or to my well-being or to my
safety to ever talk to Gamble again in my entire life.
Not to the same extent I'm a diddler but a projecting person. Okay, thank you.
I can approach Gamble.
Thank you. I just thought I forgot. I just thought maybe I was going crazy.
Could you imagine what people would say about me if I was jerking off on Omega? Oh my god
I wouldn't even be able to show my face around here again a
Widow and a single mom who has been dumped as a little cow
Who recappers and commentators such as Chris jerking off on Omega was pedophile shit. I'm sorry
You don't know a kid could come on any second
And several others
She sings
They get money. They don't want that cycle to end
He's making money off of me. Nobody died
Knows I have properly defined. I don't even jerk off in front of my cats
But what the fuck you people you people want to jerk off in front of kids on a megal
I don't even want to jerk off in front of my cats. I'll kick him out the room when I want to jerk off
I don't want my cats to sit there and watch me jerk off. That's crazy
But there is now the threat that a lot of people's money train might come to an end
Huh, that's what this is really about nobody's making money
See Gamble you're used to dealing with people who are not that bright and hey
I'll be the first to admit my brain does work slowly
But it works accurately
Cute ginger ginger the sweetheart
So you can make fun of me until the day
I'm a sweet baby. Why?
He's used to this he's used to getting annoyed. Hey ginger, you don't want to be annoyed maybe you for the past like
Five ten minutes now
Maybe you shouldn't be so fucking cute and I would leave you alone a little fucker
You're playing a very dangerous game. She said you're right. You're the biggest racist too, which is a lie
I am racist. I accept it
She said that we bought Zanders
First of all, you want it to do as you're told by Gamble, because that makes you feel good.
It makes you feel like you have a purpose.
You want it to be smooth, bro.
You didn't want there to be any bumps on the road, but you see, I'm not okay.
With a little nine-year-old girl being targeted.
Alex, are you talking to me?
You're literally the person who fucking defends pedophiles.
Then why did you choose Brain & Q over your so-called e-best online friend, Trisha?
Oh, wait, because you are okay with it.
I'm not.
Gamble's not.
You ding-bat.
I'm a 40-something-year-old.
You're a rain ranger.
I'm okay.
With your friend, Gamble, who once upon a time was dear to something special, but now...
She's mad because Gamble and Trisha agree that Brandon Kew is obsessed with her daughter?
...is on the cusp of aging out of this year.
In fact, I forgot how many years it was, and I forgot that she was even like nine years old at this point, like, because it's not in my brain, obsessing over people's kids.
...and so...
enabling and shielding that 40-something-year-old man from going after that
little girl. The hypocrisy is astounding when you inject the factor or the
element of brand and cue into the situation. It's so astounding.
That it was blatantly revealed on your own panel crystal
You gotta talk about who the fuck I was when you literally fucking used control this kid and put her on a stripper pole
And now it's drinking cakes
And Gamble was not able to get her to say that she renounces what is happening to Big Charles' daughter
You want to know why? Because she's basically a cult member
And Zayna is basically a cult leader.
Chickencake says she didn't condemn the whole school thing you dinged.
She says she condemned the school thing you dinged on, but
she doesn't want to get involved.
You dinged that.
What the fuck?
Like I said earlier, this is the same person who took an image of Controla's daughter in a Christmas outfit and put her on a fucking stripper pole and fucking edited images of all the men in the community around in the audience watching
Controla's daughter on a stripper pole. Before AI was even a thing. So she had to take all the time out of her fucking day to make that image. She didn't just type it into AI.
For that again, she said there's no mistake.
She's a fucking weirdo.
He has stated that he feels that public figure Victor De Leon, who has been outlined on rumourpedo.com, is a pedophile.
Let's rewind that. I want all of you to hear it.
But, but, but, Victor, you are a weird pedophile, and going to control this kid's school is like crazy.
One more time, just so that there's no question about it.
I mean, I mean, I mean, what's controversial about that, the pedophile hunter, no, that's gamble.
I think Alex once smug. Alex is mad that gamble rejected her.
I think so. I think you're right, Crystal.
Alex is just really mad. It doesn't really matter who's like rejects her
I think she's just mad that she's alone. She'll never have a family, you know, she'll she'll always be a lonely
I agree she's mad at gamble and Trisha agree
She doesn't want me to have anybody to support me because she did that herself. She wants to just
How me targeted little that you realize that she's in that same position like nobody fucks with her
But I don't know if you know this crystal, but everybody in this community knows about Alex
She's been doing like those two years that you were gone. Listen
those two years that you were gone and two years before that she's been in this community talking
shit about everybody calling everybody pedophiles and all that shit we all laugh at her crystal we
nobody takes her seriously everybody laughs at her don't worry no don't worry we all take it we all
laugh at it i mean for so many can you stop being it can you stop being rude to me crystal because
Seems to me that you could be working on that, but instead you're all money. What?
Can you like give me a little bit of respect around here? Are you just gonna be an asshole every time I talk?
I'm trying to listen
You're trying to listen to a fucking black pedophile
Doesn't make a lot of sense to me
Who said they gamble get your ass up here get your ass up here gamble
I'm tired of gamble
I'm tired of gamble pretending like he has all this time to sit in chat and do this and that but he can't be on the panel
It's your ass up here again
Let me finish this without you interrupting. It would go. She's live streaming. You're never gonna finish it
She'll be streaming for three hours
It's not a video it's not gonna end she'll be streaming forever. She does this all all night
He said he's doing laundry
Yeah, as if you fucking wash your clothes you greasy bastard. Don't you lie to me?
You see
It was Valentine's Day February 14th. I had someone fact-checked out for me
And it's because he has I got enough grease for both of us to be trolled
I find things were probably going to go substantially differently than they did
My god, they are sometimes
No, okay. Will you take over for a minute? Just I'm gonna order me some food. I'm hungry
You're good
Finally some bees and quiet around here
Okay, let's see who's talking in the chat
Right dickhead dickhead dickhead. Oh now I get crystal back. Oh
It's like your weaponized and mental illness game. Well, I
In my mind at this rate, you're never gonna eat
Everything closes at like nine in Oklahoma
But they could always play this particular clip if you wanted to
And why does the AI image make your titties look like your titties are not that big play the clip where I just own him oh
Your titties are not that big. I don't know why you have that picture the AI picture made your titties look that big
They're not that big
promise
Again, that was April 30th. I didn't know him and I could tell the cops
I really didn't know him knew nothing about him just threw a name out there now that I know him. I stay away
Yeah, he's he did he
I'll fucking team up with a I don't this guy this woman is so crazy
Just know if you ever piss me off. I'm gonna play that clip over and over
Wait, she's making fun of gambling autistic
I just thought he was very prodigal and a lot like you're the one that calls yourself
Well, actually, it's your friend gamble who is
Normalizing that label on Zeta at this point. I mean gamble. He's a lot more popular than me
I've been saying that Zeta is a PDF for a long time
But now you have gamble saying it and you know if he's still trying to play
Okay, but the difference is Gamble and I agree that he just stayed far away from me.
Alex was trying to hang out with her and what, no, no, no, listen, Alex was trying to hang
out with Zaya and be her fucking friend.
And then Zaya was like, I don't want to, I don't want to hang out with you or whatever.
And Alex got mad.
That Alex, that was Alex's shit.
Alex went to Florida to hang out with him.
now can I talk to you okay but gamble isn't trying to play matchmaker with me
in a pdf you ding dong that's what alex is doing
hold on let me give me a snack because you don't ever shut up
okay let's go sorry yeah you need something else to put in your mouth
besides air shut up you shut up
hello why did you bring my coaster out here you ding dong
okay let's go back sorry i'll fucking stick my knee up your ass
Yeah, I'm still a young hip guy. I'm not exactly artistically inclined, but, you know, I'm whipping.
Everyone knows about me because of Aaron Carter, even though I try to pretend like I'm against Aaron Carter.
If I worked for Aaron Carter, there would be no gamble.
Yeah.
Let's keep going.
Gamble is around way before Aaron.
A lot of these people are new fags.
Because he's sick in the head and you know that, Gamble, but
you do appear to have made some sort of a truce or agreement with him.
And now you're having some issues because you want the attention again, Gamble
I guess it's been three years since you weren't supposed to be on YouTube
Now you want to make your comeback
You want to be the PDF Hunter, but you don't want to go after any difficult targets
He's never said he's a PDF Hunter. It's not hard to be a PDF Hunter. They're fucking everywhere
Haha, maybe you're trying to set up a situation using crystal to get him. What I don't think that's gonna work
Yeah, well you see how sick these people are they're like that worried about the internet
Oh, yeah, I was making a couple doing this like it's just like so real to them
So
You might want to start what are you doing? What are you eating crystal?
There's like these crackers that have they taste like sesame like what are they called?
My mom got it
There's the Cm multi green eight seed crackers
There's Disney Channel crackers
I
Think that you do think it's funny. I think that you think that people are no clue
This is my favorite channel my favorite chat all the all the realest niggas come to this chat swear to God
We're not fucking around.
We're against PDFs around here.
We don't fuck with Alex.
She's a PDF supporter.
Fuck her.
Nobody takes her seriously. We've all been laughing at Alex for the last four years. She's literally a fucking clown
Everything that comes out of her mouth. Nobody takes any stock in it and if they do then they're just as fucking retarded as she is
From two years ago three years ago five years ago are relevant whereas they're not I
Find it astounding that you've mentioned me as much as you have. I'm not relevant
Have a very small audience. We all know you're not you're not relevant. We all know
Maintain fucking relevance around here, bitch. We all know fuck out of here
You're just you're just an old black bitch who wishes that she had a fucking baby and a husband
And that's why you're so depressed in your life because you never had a fucking family
You wish that you had the same life that just Jen does you literally?
That's why you obsess over just Jen so much.
Oh, an ex porn star who got her shit together, has a family,
has a child, has a happy life seemingly.
Not everybody's life is perfect, but I mean, shit,
she got a better life than you do.
Hopping around from Airbnb to Airbnb.
I have you, man.
You're my dad.
I can support a pedophile, Alex.
Fuck out of here, nigga.
And everybody questions my fucking methods.
I don't get it.
I don't even have a little brother baby.
Alex lived her entire life hopping from Airbnb to Airbnb. She doesn't even live in a in a in a in a place
I don't know if you know that but she doesn't live in one place
She goes from Airbnb to Airbnb because she's afraid when Tommy James met her in real life
Tommy James said that like when she went they went to the grocery store
She ran into the grocery store and when she came out she ran back to the car. That's how afraid she is
That's how like scared. She is in real life
Yeah
She's not the same person that she is on the internet, I promise
She's not that person
She's not a fucking gangster
See you're counting on not as many people watching you Dan, but you're counting on people
Not being able to comprehend certain things and you're counting on things being
Approximately the same as they were when you were heavily active in your prime
things have changed
So you got to adapt to the times or be left behind
Why does she act like such a white person? I don't know
If I talked like that the opposite way like any bonnix feel be like why are you being a wigger?
She's like a week. She's like uh, she's like uh, which is very interesting. Oh we get
I don't even know what to call her
She's an Oreo
But she wants to take up for the black community you grew up in a white neighborhood Alice you grew up around white people
Why do you think you sound an act like that?
She lives in you're a white person
Alex is one of the whitest people I've ever heard on these streams as a matter of fact
You don't have to make a lot of money to live incredibly well in the state of Oklahoma
I'm gonna start shaming about gamble
Gamble we're gonna go
I'm gonna start making gamble exposed dreams
I'm seeing red
You wouldn't be able to like game no gamble gamble. You shouldn't like gambling. Please don't tell me you like gambling
That's one of like a man's
For men, that's like the biggest crutch
There's sex and gambling is like the biggest crutches of men. Please don't get into gambling god damn it gamble
I thought you were smarter than the gamble
Even if you have a lot of money don't gamble, please
I grew up around a lot of people who made a lot of money off of other people gambling if you know what I mean
It's gonna do it
And she was always proclaiming that she's an Oklahoma girl
And I asked her one day, I'm like, how come at every convention, you're always yelling and screaming about being an Oklahoma girl and she was like, I don't tell you, Monica.
I used to be known as Monica for some of you who don't know.
When did I ever like, because I was so freaking happy to get out of that shit.
What?
That's how is it beautiful saying
I'm more of a Louisiana girl that likes crawfish and show what the fuck
that was one of the things my dad always told me he was like you know you can
smoke weed and you can be such a you can be a drunk but just on gamble no that
was what you said Alex no that's what we said about you because you said that
Alex nobody said someone was gonna put semen inside me what the fuck
Yeah, stop eating in the mic crystal. You're you're making everybody upset. I'm sorry. It's crunchy. Okay, so
She literally just said that game was once to put semen in me. That's not what he said
we he said
Alex yeah, go ahead and take brain and semen or psyche or whatever or what?
There was there certain people like I
Don't even want to talk about it. I shouldn't even talk about that
But just know that gambling is not a good thing
That's not true
On anything I don't care if it's $20. Don't gamble
$20 and buy you and your girlfriend some McDonald's don't gamble
She's single and available
What she's the size of the child
What does that mean
What if he has a chatter now mean he has her own home and I could stream from there what?
She's a streamer thirsty for clout and attention to just like me
What she likes to bully people left and right oh
Oh
She has one now
The crazy thing is that that's been going on for years. Is she copying my what's right now? She's copying me
No, I mean she's jealous of you crystal come on let her be jealous
Let her be a jellyfish.
She is a jellyfish.
She's mad because when she goes live, Crystal,
nobody types in her chat.
You can ask Anvil.
Anvil just came in here to report back to me
that she has one person in her chat,
and that was an hour ago that I was talking about that.
I know Q, I know Q, I know Q.
Without me.
Here we go again with the stupid clip.
She's brought up this clip like so, too.
They're not really exactly desirable.
But is it?
You're these fucking Negro mites as content.
I like this.
She doesn't admit it, but she's watching all the streams all the time
She's not oh, yeah. Well, that's all you do too, bitch
Alex you're gonna pretend like you don't watch all the streams all the time then how do you know about everything?
Alex how do you know about everything that happens if you don't watch all the streams that doesn't make any sense
Fuck out of here
Because she also she recently asked you you know Q45
Yeah, the sexiest motherfucker alive. I
Just haven't recapped it yet
Recap it bitch. You're the one stuck in my dick
Alex wants me to suck her dick so bad. It's crazy, and I will never do it and never have
She's so weird cool girl. She's mad because she doesn't have a celebrity in a sex symbol on her panel
She can't bring me down I'm a gangster
You know who I am crystal ball I'm a gangster
She's bringing up she's talking about psyche now what a fucking loony tune
What a crazy person
in that little rant of his.
He don't want to rape you, he wants to make love to you.
What?
I'm wondering, were y'all ever talking behind the scenes?
I got you on.
It's better than you're...
I don't know him.
It's better than your clown look at me.
Do you think I'm not me and you?
No.
Pray up.
Oh, you and Zaya?
Yeah.
Oh yeah, obviously you never talked behind the scenes.
Mm-hmm
Why does it matter what state I live in because they're trying to dox you
But the difference is crystal now is that you got way more crazy niggas that are on your side that are against you
There's way more niggas that are willing to fuck it listen yes it ain't it ain't 2022 anymore
incredibly low self esteem which is the exact kind of I'm beautiful I love myself
See, I think she's a blood fish
I love myself even if I was about it might end up being single forever
Definitely not as ugly as Alex is I mean Alex has Alex sister and takes fucking 10-inch monster dick
Stuff or pussy and fucking fries about it
I mean at least you'd never had at least at least Chris the land never got to a low point in her life to where she had to sell her
Pussy on camera for a couple thousand dollars
Now this is gamble
Manipulating crystal nobody's not master extraordinary
really listen to how he talks to her.
Really listen, okay?
Chris, well, you are so many men's type, okay?
Not mine, but I'm sure a lot of other people-
I am a lot of men's type.
Oh, well, I'm half Asian.
I don't understand my family. They only take charge like maybe a maybe three to five thousand dollars for a porn scene
Alexandra mayors, where's that money at all that money that you accepted for taking a fucking fat dick up your ass
You don't have it anymore. It wasn't long term. You're a fucking idiot. You're not me a califa
Brought as stupid not considering how evil you are.
You're evil, Batman, the Zorro world, Batman.
You're not the real Cardi is a grown woman, but I don't know what the fuck she was thinking.
I don't know what the hell Cardi was thinking.
Gamble, what the hell was Cardi thinking, letting that fucking idiot in his in her house?
And it's not even it's not even listen.
It's not even the fact that he's a PDF is what I'm thinking.
It's the fact that having Zaya living in your house
just brings a bunch of attention, like.
I understand letting pebs live there, but Zaya that's crazy. That's crazy. That's my name
Come on, bro. That's crazy. I know y'all love Cardi Lee. I know she's like a loyal
She's you know, she's DX. She's like one of the OG DX motherfuckers, but letting Zaya live in your crib is crazy
Sorry, and I know you can be mad you can be mad at however you want about it, but that's crazy
And and I'll be honest with you. Cardi Lee has donated me probably like $2,000
Brain and Q is her one viewer. Cardi Lee is one of my biggest Cardi Lee is one of my biggest
Donators of all time
Comment. No, let me let me spit my shit. Let me spit my shit Cardi Lee is one of my biggest
Donators of all time and
I love her. She's a she's a super kind hearted loving woman
I know why the I know why you let pebs in your crib because you know
You wanted her to get away from Zea, but then you got Zea living there, too
Like what the fuck how you gonna have a Zea living in your crib?
That's crazy
that's fine oh he's giving her the pass to call somebody get it i wonder how she uses
to be hard but how you gonna let zaya live in your crib also zaya is literally living in her
attic and she's creating zaya is living in cardi lee's attic and creating war with people
like okay for example can you pause this please crystal please crystal can you please pause this
can we please have a conversation for a second because this is some real shit done
This is some real shit. Can you please pause this? Nobody wants to hear about this fucking this n-word. Thank you
Jesus Christ
What she's almost done. Can we finish it?
She's almost done. You've been saying that for fucking 30 minutes look bro
She doesn't ever fucking quit look it's like at the end
Oh, wow, she's gonna sit there and she's gonna cry about Chris. She's gonna say the same thing
But what new is she what new shit is she gonna say crystal? Please tell me
Fucking Christ defend me Q defend me
I don't need to defend you. I know
I'm not but the thing is I'm five five two. I was five three. Yeah, like I was I mean, yeah
I don't need to offend you on the internet. I mean in real life. Yeah, you're five foot two. I mean
You're you're a girl obviously I defend you I'll defend you in real life
I don't care what people look like I think like I really don't care what people look like and
Also, the fact that you're making fun of doors like after and the reason why I call pray of that is because he made fun of
Kate's child who has a genetic way. I'm making fun of who I'm making fun of who?
Who I said pray yeah, yeah
Oh, Zea was making fun of Kate's trouble who has a genetic condition
But here she is making fun of that genetic condition, but trying to put it on me listen. I love we man
Let her destroy herself cue. Oh
Gosh
No, he's just I agree
Let me talk papa who is like an annoying little brother that doesn't ever shut up during the movie
you just won't let me say what I have to say say whatever you want to say you
won't pause the video while I have to say it though the whole point that I was
making was the preface love Cardi Lee you've been generous you've donated me a
The fact that you let Zaya live in your fucking crib is crazy
And I'm not gonna and I'm not gonna sit here and like a lot of people are afraid to say this or they don't want to you know
A lot of people are afraid to like speak their mind
Cardi leave that shit's fucking crazy. You're like one of the most og fucking DX members
And you got a fucking a legitimate PDF living in your fucking crib
New of Katie at 16. I didn't start talking to her until she was 17.
I didn't move her into my house until she was 18.
Come on, bro. I'm come on.
That's just crazy.
That's just absolutely fucking wild.
To be honest, I didn't even know anything about cardedly.
Like, honestly, I don't think you can't like.
They you have to talk to them because I want to go get one of my hips, you know.
No, actually, I can charge I understand I understood why she let pebs in there at in the first place because originally it was just pebs that
Went to live at Cardi Lee's crib, right?
Which is fine because I was like, oh, yeah, she's he's she finally saving her from that fucking weirdo
Maybe pebs can get her life together this and that
Then they go to live there and I was like, oh shit. Here we go. It's it's a fucking
I make like almost 80,000 a year and she lives off of an inheritance. So whatever. She's jealous
Listen a lot of people might be listen
I know a lot of these motherfuckers, especially like older old-school DX motherfuckers. They might be scared or
You know, they might talk shit about me saying that but I'll say it right out here
And she's dead. I mean you were DX you donated. You're a huge donor of mine. So I have no listen
My
You've been talking forever. Let me talk. No, you've been talking forever mother
Alex Alex was talking forever not me
Don't blame Alex because of me. Um, anyways, can I just say one one thing? So no, no, no, no, no, no, Anita blood
You can't make it a fucking non-dx issue. That's a fucking pop out. That's a cop out that any who?
Um, sorry, my brother is annoying. Um, Anita. That's a cop out
That's not a
She's a grown woman who can make her own choice. Okay. Anyways, so Alex when she when I met with her
She was like really really
Shut up annoying brother
So she was obsessed with gamble. She was like really like, oh, I'd love to date gamble and all this stuff
And I'm thinking this one's a cougar the hell is wrong with this Alex Myers girl like what so I think what's happening is
She's very jealous of me. I'm taking
Gamble has a fiance. She's jealous because, you know, he would never give Alex a freaking chance like that
But the thing is is she's so mad that she ruined her friendship with Trisha not me
She did right so and she's upset because I don't know maybe the money of her inheritance
It's like going away, but I think I'm pretty stuck for myself where I can't afford my own home
My own bills have a nice home for just myself. Who knows?
maybe
If I ever get married then I could upgrade Alex. Are you gonna be jealous of that?
Like I think I'm doing pretty fine for myself at 37
I've always lived on my own and it didn't matter what it doesn't matter how much your house is or what state you're in as long as I
Have a roof over my head and I'm proud of my pride of my shit. That's all that matters. I
Can accomplish things in life
If I want to Tommy wants to join. Is that the real Tommy? Yeah it is. I'm sick of Tommy too. I
Can't hear you Tommy. Crystal in I can't okay. Hi. Are you me? No? I'm not born bombing you. We're good. What's up Q45?
It's like pulling a weird name narrative of gamble and I
I'm surprising you with a shower cameo crystal. Oh
My god, I was all like whoa Tommy get naked. I don't want a porn bomb
He's not gonna show his dick, but he does this all the time
Hey, just don't have your phone slipped and then we see something he won't he won't show his dick
He doesn't I'll make sure the camera doesn't drop
Okay
You better have your cameras fucking waterproof and one to my stream where the party's been at all day
Cheers to the freaking weekend I drink to that. Yeah
You
Let the gym is on sink and I drink to that. Yeah. Yeah
Don't let the bastards get you down
Two can you stop being annoying?
Crystal are you okay in this?
Q can you hear me?
Yes, hello. I
Didn't hear you I
Can hear crystal crystal probably can't hear me
Crystal has an iPhone I have a galaxy
Yeah, this is the one-time galaxy owners win
This is stream yard always favors the galaxies all
Iphones always have issues on fucking stream yard throughout the years if you're a real nigger, you know that sure
iPhones always have issues on stream yard. Yeah
Crystal how have you been cradled?
Did you call me quiddle what a rare?
That's what Wilbur used to call me
Tommy James is doing
Fucking porn bombing you can't even see that little button in a bush
Shut up Q. I
Wanted to finish what Alex was saying and you've really interrupted like you're like that one. Why do you care about that fucking?
Troglodyte Gorilla
You guys are ruining my content with your nonsense
Your content is yourself
You are your content
I know
Crystalline is Crystalline's content
I'm doing commentary on a mentally old person
Crystalline's content is Crystalline's content
I'm good
Q is very like annoying right now
He really needs to be hit
You're annoying
You're more annoying than me
I'm not screaming at the top of my lungs. I'm pretty chill. I'm like you. Yeah, because you have neighbors
So why is q45 y'all the top of his mom's that's really rude
Hmm Tommy James. I don't want to hear
We just have a brother sisterly relationship and it's like a love-hate relationship, you know
He likes to tell me what to do. I like to do 45 it's been sabotaging your streams purposely be careful for still and I
Know for some reason our dynamic
I know you know I'm sabotaging your streams
Even though Tommy James is in the shower where he could flip his camera down and show his dick at any second
No, he was funny I like you
Tommy you're not gonna you're not gonna work your fucking you're low IQ fucking
Pulling up with the bug stop stop are you in with each other be nice gosh
You I'm gonna kill I'm gonna kill Tommy. No, don't why would you say that you're rude?
I'm gonna murder
You're being
Okay, I'm gonna fuck him. I'm gonna cut his titties off and put on where his dick was
I let you talk for an extra five minutes and that extra five minutes is going cuz man. Tell me you're cool
We're just fucking around
Like I can't deal with I want to cut his titties off. What's wrong with that?
Jesus Christ, look at the look at them things they make some good
I'm not racist
You're a fucking 2 o'clock plan number
I'm not racist you're part of the QQQ
And like I said, in these communities, you are in good company, but in the real world, you're not, but let's keep going.
And it's like the song that never ends.
You know, RG is a bully.
Polly, can you disable your camera at me?
Making me nervous.
RG is a bully, and he's a really sick individual.
from this particular live stream.
You can't let RG, you can't let RG run your chat anymore.
I like RG, stop Q.
Yeah, but he's a really, he's a really evil purple.
Oh, you're getting muted.
Now let me listen
Sorry Q you left
Come back
Come back. I won't be mean
Q come back Q come back
Why is this woman like weirdly obsessed with me?
Q come back
Hi Q
Hi his face showed hi
Hello
This is Q's face. Dang boy. Look at them craters
Can you hear me Q?
Look at that perky pristine skin
He looks so sad
Oh my god, don't do that. You really are my return to little brother
What is why are you doing this cute cute? Don't do that again
Don't say that
I are you saying that because I can't hear you anything I didn't say anything
Y'all this is right. This is why I said he got hit and ugly
Oh my y'all the problem with Q is he was born with fetal aqua health syndrome
Yeah, I'm a crack baby. I told you already. I'm a crack baby
I'm so crazy. I'm a crack baby
Exaggerating for like sympathy. Okay. Anyways, you got dropped on the head a few times as a baby
It's all right, bitch excuse me
Go ahead bitch. Okay. Go hit your head on the wall ten times like you always did as a kid
You might have hit a door in your face because I will
You stupid bitch are you done speaking idiot or can I speak English?
You speak idiot I speak English. I don't know what you're trying to do here
Seems like a major deflection
Sounds like he lost a lot of brain cells over the two years. I was gone
Sounds like I'm by the shirts and cities
Oh my gosh, I can't look I'm sorry that my brother is so embarrassing
He always shows his face how much did you drink tonight?
I always show my face. Are you kidding me? I'm a celebrity in a sex symbol. Everybody knows what I look like
I've committed fucking felonies on camera. You're not a sex symbol. Stop saying that
Oh my god
I'm a sex symbol and that's my criminal
I don't understand what I don't understand why crystal is so like worried about me showing my face crystal
I don't understand the absolute mania that
You've never you you were you weren't around to see my absolute maniac streak
You have no idea about the shit that I did.
You look better than you did three years ago.
You have no fucking idea, bro.
Tommy James.
Tommy James, you know what I'm talking about.
Yeah, you go loony too.
She has no fucking clue, bro.
I don't.
That's why I don't play around too much.
She's not learned.
He'll fuck you.
He'll mess your life.
He'll waste your whole life.
And I look younger than him.
By the way, I look like shit right now because the only the only the only thing I watch like
Oh, is this fucking scar because I got fucking I got whacked with a I got whacked with a folding chair when I was like
13 years old and I've had this red-ass scar here ever since
That's why Barb she's super paranoid
Clean clean. She's afraid. She's afraid of her own shadow. Literally. You should see her walk around at the grocery store.
Tommy James you're balding Tommy you're balding. I'm not balding dog. You are balding.
Show Tommy. Look at that hairline. Show Tommy. Show Tommy. Look at that hairline. Look at that hair.
Look at that hair.
Show Tommy. That's what I thought.
I just have a big forehead. I just have a big no, we're balding bro. You don't
Trust me Tommy Tommy Tommy I encourage you to go back and look at streams of you from three four years ago and compare
Trust me. It was the same dude my hair
I got a nice head of hair. It's beautiful.
This is coming from a nigga who monitors his hairline.
I'm telling you.
Dude, I had long hair when I was in high school,
long before you were even born. Calm down.
Calm enough. I was no you were not in high school before I was born
You're not that much
Tommy you're not that much
Look at that beautiful. How can you say I'm going bald?
No, I didn't say you were going bald. I said your hairline was getting a little bit thin. I got a thin hair. Okay
Okay, I didn't say you're going bald obviously you wouldn't have the hair that you did if you were going bald
I said it's starting a little sensitive at the beginning stages. It's going right. It's going and tell me tell me
I also recognize maybe which is weird Alex. I also recognize that you know
Eventually for me, it's gonna go as well. You know, I get it. It's gonna start of the man. I get it
We got all get used to it
I'm just glad I was tall. I'm just I'm just glad I was tall
Men go ball because imagine if you were short and black a testosterone going on
Well, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no the so supposedly the more testosterone you have the faster your hair
Goes away if you ever heard about that study
The faster you go bald or you have a receding hairline
Well, you know some men they have it a different way like some men they recede on the hairline and some men they recede on their crown in the back
But I'm the type of motherfucker bro like I said I've been saying this for years as soon as I started seeing it going Tommy
I'm not lying. I just rather be bald
and i'll just start buying hats i'll just wear hats the rest of my life i can't be i'm not gonna
look like i'm not gonna look like ld and mr burns bro i'm not gonna look like ld you're not gonna be
like that's crazy no when i met stony in real life when i met stony in well listen when i met stony
in real life i even said that they were like bro you should probably let it go he's like no i only
have a few years left with hair it looks worse now than it would if you just fucking went bald
Just, just go on!
I don't know why he doesn't just shave it. He looks pretty hard with the shave.
I haven't seen, I haven't seen that dude in like over a year. Like on stream or in real life.
Yeah, are you subbed to his channel? He goes live still.
No, I'm, no, that's what I said. I haven't seen him.
Over a year on stream or a real life. I still watch poppin as live streams. I like Tony's
Both the all for a minute. Thank you
Up cute before I hit you with the door. Let me talk. Okay
We're gonna Alex. I was never fixated on ski. That was you
Hey, I know I don't even understand why you're bringing up cakes into this and you did one tools, baby
She came onto my stream and completely said that was true. So what lies, huh?
What you
Are insane you are so obsessed with me
to say hi I don't want people she doesn't like white people everyone to shut up
and like gamble talk because y'all two are annoying me sorry what no fuck gamble
I don't like you gamble you better
so this is the first time I'm going and left forever and you're gonna tell me
that I'm fucking offended I'm out of here that was cute I like you for I like
You better stop denying the fact that you were a chubby little bastard a couple like me
But because you said that I hear I have a clip of me two weeks before I ever showed up on ice beside in stream here
Just three and I want to see it. I want to see it. Please. Please. I'm literally thinner
That is a holy holy AI
That's literally my ex's house, dude. You can say a lot of weight
No, you look normal now. You stopped doing drugs.
Maybe like 10, 15 pounds. Yeah, I did stop using so many drugs. That's true.
How do you feel about Alex putting this false narrative on you?
Maybe you have a different camera, but you're a lot tanner now.
You used to look like pale back then like Tom and James pale.
Yeah, I used to not go out like that, but now I free dive and jet ski and stuff.
Are you still doing that?
Yeah, just not as often but I just got back into doing it again because the Jets he needed to be repaired
But like I was watching you do it and do it and kick I
Clumsy, and then I didn't see yeah
I still I still go live on kick a few times a week and when I do make it out there on the kick streams
I show what I do so you still have that gate chest tattoo
Hey crystal be careful for clumsy. He's an Alex Mayer's fucking
The tribal the tribal one
Okay, so all this stuff that Alex was saying about you, what do you want to say?
Who Alex the crazy one how she's like
As you try to push on well, I don't know I wasn't I wasn't kidding like I was watching you in queue
And I think you were listening to her
But you have to understand like trying to listen to what she says through your stream is like very difficult to keep up with
I could just hear pieces like I I've get that she's trying to say that I'm manipulating you so that
Zaya goes to you to say a party party
But like everybody nobody unfortunately the situation is that Cardi
has put herself in that situation and none of us would have ever suggested or agreed to that if
anybody had to say it but she's her own person so like what the fuck I'm not going to go out of my
way to try to save her from somebody she's giving money to she's posting about why she's doing it
right so you know how earlier we were just like saying you know we can have self defense or whatever
you know she's trying to say that we threaten Zaya now what
and now she's saying she because she's just come up to my place and she put up
there's certain things there's certain things that you have to like when you hear these people
say they're just trying to say them to get that growl you up you know what i mean
some things are real some things are bullshit you can't just like take every single thing that
Okay, so you're trying to give her what she wants to be honest. I mean, I know it's me
You're meeting me like I'm the only one who thinks this
Um, I think remember
Reacting to people like Alex like people are saying oh you're giving her what she wants. I mean
That's true. It's Crystal's prerogative who she like look I first told Crystal that the best thing to do with Brandon Q
Is to not pay attention to them
Restreaming her and so I said if you know that he's restreaming you you can play clips of him being a petto and he'll turn it off
That may also, people could argue you're giving him what he wants by addressing him, but that's beneficial, right?
Yeah.
So if there are a bunch of people watching at the same time, if Crystal's live at the same time Alex is and she thinks,
oh, well, I could just go and respond to it for a little while, I don't think that's necessarily giving Alex what she wants,
because Alex is in here watching Crystal's live anyways, trying to clip stuff to like those things.
Gamble of that logic, that logic only applies directly, listen, listen, Crystal.
Crystal that logic directly only applies to Zeya because he doesn't care whether you're saying nice things or if you're calling
That applies the brain and Q as well same exact thing
And she's been defaming gamble nice saying that we started this no it was
Alex is like so hated
Nobody takes Alex seriously. I've been playing this for hours.
Nobody takes Alex seriously.
We made that kind of order, though.
There's an angle where in 2026,
Crystal Lann, who used to be many people's low cow,
is now low cowing Alex.
I don't think it's giving her what she wants.
Exactly. Exactly.
The title.
People want content.
Alex right now is the content
because everybody hates Alex right now.
I mean, she's-
Everybody has always hated Alex.
She's inserting herself into this and then trying to pretend like she doesn't want anything to do with it.
She wants attention. Alex knows that Brandon's a PDF. Alex knows all this shit.
She understands that she's trying to go against the grain for attention.
But the thing is, okay, what you don't understand is nobody expected her to turn on Gamble the way she did.
Alex isn't this stupid, okay? She might act like she's stupid, but she knows Brandon's a pedophile.
C'mon.
She's telling us that gamble is around my street.
That is what people want to watch right now.
No, she just wants attention and she's scraping the ground for attention, and Brandon happens
I don't care.
This is my panel.
Crystal, why?
You get so mad at him.
I don't know why.
For no reason.
Because he's so annoying.
You guys are saying the same thing is for everyone, most of everyone in the chat likes
you and Q.
Together
Draping the ground for content
Happens to be the fucking soil
Tommy
It's better than people screaming at each other. At least people have context. At least there's context that I give with my content
context and substance
That's been missing in the panel versus you
It's okay for Crystal to respond to stuff and move on if she goes live tomorrow and is like
Fuck Alex again for like ever
Somewhere and if I'm giving
Huh, I did just want to say I just want to say while Q's here, uh, you know, I know you before as Obi-Wan
From I remember yeah, I've been around these communities a long fucking time
I think for me, I remember before coronavirus it would have been going into 2019. I think or maybe in 2020
I don't know that may have been no, it was no, you're right. You're right
It was going into tonight because this is before coronavirus. I know exactly I know based on where I was living at the time
When I was talking to you and being Obi-Wan, that was in 2018 into 19.
So that was even way before fucking coronavirus.
Yeah, that would that would that would have been November actually of 2018.
That was before I had ever even fucking show my face or was on a streamer panel.
That was before I even knew what streamer was.
I thought he was like a 40 year old dude.
I thought he was probably going to be like Shmiggy or something
because of how he typed and and his uh
Handle as Obi-Wan Kenobi. I just assumed you would be like fucking 38 or some shit back then
And then you ended up doing the streams and they said that you're Obi-Wan, and I thought that was awesome
No, you're older if you're older than you're fucking Ben Kenobi if you're younger, you know, I grew up with Obi-Wan Kenobi
That's true like I'm trying to like you you're like
You're 28. Okay, so you're older. I knew you were younger, but I thought maybe it was a little younger, but that makes sense then that makes
Yeah, he's nine years younger than me. That's why he's my little bro. I was born in February 28th 1998
Okay 98 there you go
Good. Well, I mean I just wanted to, you know, tell you that I always loved you as a chatter
And I saw many of your streams too, and we liked them also
We stopped watching it. No, you've been on my panels many times. Yeah
I don't remember what was happening because I didn't pay enough attention
But I think you were like fighting people in the streets or something screaming n words in the street or something nutty
It went from you being at home to being a little more aggressive out in the streets
So after you were after you were joining my streams
I kind of had like a little bit of a I got evicted from that apartment and I had a little bit of a crackdown period
Where I was going crazy and basically that that crash out led me all the way to, California from pennsylvania
and
I crossed out a little bit here, and now I'm like in this predicament now where I'm like working and living in an apartment
Do you know what I missed? Oh, I missed you
Oh, hey, I hope you're doing well, bro. I always hope you're doing well
I hope you're doing well too, man. You gotta be on scene and shoulda hope y'all are happy
I miss when you just got Oofy on your streams and making yell at his mom and crash out at his little apartment
Oofy got like, fucking what, ten years probation or something for fucking nothing?
dreams
probably did it on your streams
i think oofy joined my stream
maybe once or twice
he was in like a big stage
i created oofy unfortunately
and then he went all out
going on sale
well w oofy
oofy had a major
crash out nobody would have
played
that was a little bit too much
that motherfucker went crazy
No, but listen at least he did it to like the like some
I'm sorry crystal. He's I'm glad that I'm glad that if he did fucking Victor at least he did it to some fucking actual
Before I hit you with the door and brand nobody's doxing anybody
Yeah, I'm just saying I'm glad Oofy did what he did to Zaya. That's all
Like Z Diddy I prefer Z Diddy you like pray up. Yeah
But the thing is is so Alex seems to have this weird fantasy like I'm inviting Zay to my place a fuck no
I mean prayer. I don't want him near me. I don't like I don't understand
Apparently, that's why I'm here crystal to make it happen
I'm here to match you with Victor De Leon.
Oh, yeah, and the fact that she's like saying that.
This nigga, Gamble, is always trying to help me a little bit.
We're saying that you're the biggest racist of all of us.
I didn't know that was like a secret, I'm sorry.
Apparently, you're the biggest racist.
No, but nobody knows me unless and that was before everything showed in my face.
That was like so long ago
Stop you're being rude to him and gamble doesn't come on
I promise he's fine. I like him Q and I go way back. He watched my streams before you did
Like 20 then
Well, I'm 28 well that was no that was in 2020 so that I was probably like 22. I knew him when he was like 25
Because I remember I remember where I was watching you based on where I lived at the time and I moved in that place in 2020
So it had to have been
Like okay, okay at least me when I'm responding to Alex. I give people's context
Substance she started things right?
Crystal don't talk of this. I tell you to it's puppet master time
Yeah, Chris, shut your mouth
Okay, Chris, you're good. I always think of my little annoying brother, you know?
Chris, you're good. You can talk again.
Anyway, so Alex called Gamble the biggest racist of them all.
Good girl. He said he's the most evil, and he's trying,
and she's trying to make it sound like he's like abusive and stuff.
I have multiple Native American ancestry, okay?
Right. I resent that.
And she's saying, she made some shit up about your,
you being like Puerto Rican or something, but you're actually Cuban.
That's so wrong my dad is from Argentina. I mean Argentina and Anita's Cuban. I am an American
you're a fucking white boy did you know that my mother's family were knights in
England and then renounced and then came over on the Mayflower one of you gave
the right answer one of the American family were they're on the ledger for
Listen, my great-great-great-great-great-great-great grandfather married a Native American woman in the same colony at the same time as Pocahontas.
So, right. Alex called Gable the N-word. Many, many times she said that he is doing and that I'm only...
being with Gamble for a smooth ride it has not been a smooth ride since Alex
interfered and butted in to our business when Brandon Q was talking about a
smooth ride. Gamble's cock is very veiny. Relax. Q you're being weird.
I'm joining on my laptop. I think this device is...
Yeah, I'm having trouble.
Wait, did this Tommy meet Alex Mayer?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm the one who fucked Alex Mayer.
Yeah, you fucking, he fucked Tahi.
His dick has been inside.
Oh, what is the matter with you?
What the fuck is the matter with you?
Listen Gamble before he met her, I tried to tell him that she had AIDS and I tried to tell him that he was a crazy psycho!
Tell me that I want to listen to you!
As a meme, I want to listen to you!
I haven't turned down my youthful voice, sorry.
Oh yeah, apparently he was an utter liar.
Tommy, were you the one who fucked Alex Mayers?
Oh no.
How does she how do you feel that she was comparing you to bring you like y'all are alive? That was weird
Weird bro
You said that she had a lot of discharge out of her pussy. Yes or no
I don't want to hear this shit
No, we already said this on your panel, Christo. Let him do his testimony and then we never have to do it again
But I need to hear it
Okay, uh
Fucking long story short. She uh
Yeah, she had lots of discharging. It's not like poop and tuna mixed in a bowl stir it around
Her nickname has been
They call her starship
They call her poop tuna now. It's poop tuna. Okay. But does not nobody remember when Preston
Messed with her. He's the one that went around saying that she had like HIV and AIDS
He's the one that was lost in her house. I did get tested. No AIDS. No AIDS. You did? Okay. What's going on with my mic?
Is my mic all fucked up?
From hearing this it's a girl we're echoing from somebody
Does it mean I'm gonna leave and join back on my
Yeah, Crystal you have to rejoin we can't agree I think y'all I can hear y'all can y'all hear me
I was doing the same thing to honestly
But yeah, oh there goes the echo
Yeah, um
Anyways, I would say yeah, I know people will keep telling me to ignore Alex
But she keeps going on she brought is a into this and then nobody's saying for you to ignore Alex
Yeah, you can talk with me all the shit you want about Alex
But a lot of people like why let people go watch her video when they can listen people are telling you to people are telling you to
Ignore Zaya because Zaya feeds on attention whether you're calling him pedophile
He keeps bringing him up not me. Listen. Say it. Listen. Listen Zaya thrives off of any attention
Whether you're talking about him as in a good light or a bad light
So many people gamble music based Marty came across him and they're like, oh, he just loves his attention. I'm not giving it to him
Okay, but let me say this Alex literally threatened saying she doesn't live far for me
And she will come over here to like
Dumb black bitch. So what if her and prayer were to team up and then they come to my place like that's not stupid
Alex's last name is because of let me talk so gamble. She says be honest that prayer could use the clip
Where we are using self-defense, but she's trying to use that beta clip where I said team up for him to be for it
It'd be okay for him to sit there and come to my place
because
He's saying that the reason zaya pretends he's gonna go somewhere
But then doesn't is because he knows that if he shows up he'll get blasted wherever he goes
But he showed up to alex
I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet, but I don't know yet,
That's true. He is only comfortable. But why is why is Alex advocate? I wish you
Love me so I could really go crazy on the motherfucker like oh my god
When has Victor at all this dry all this pulling up on everyone Alex controller, whatever
Why has he never pulled up on one guy?
My state for a long time. He said he was coming to my dad's when I live
Hold on
It's a big list. He said he was gonna pull up on me blackout Andy and blogger all in the same breath
Then made a big excuse saying oh, I'm on yeah
He walks it back and he always
Reasons why he can't if I go there if I go there, they're just gonna call the cops
So why am I gonna go there? Well, why are you saying you're gonna fucking go there then if you know that that's
He said he'd fly me to Florida to and pay for the ticket me moon walked on that too
real person who is like like upset with somebody and wants to do something to them first off you don't
Headline it before you kind of just
And a gate isn't gonna stop you and cops aren't gonna stop you or whatever because you actually don't give a fuck
He likes to pretend to be that sort of man
Not he's a tiny little
People like controller. I wish you would pull up on me the same way that you pulled up on controller because I
I would love oh my god. It would be a field day. You have no idea
Controller was sitting there in her car at the beach like smoking a joint. I wish
I wish nigga a short low nigga like you would pull up on me like that. Oh my god
I would nail you down boy
You better bring your gun
Question yeah, do you think that if there was less baldness in the world that there would be less rapey pedophiles?
Yes
Branding Q is just a weirdo, and I think I think I think I think the Internet has created a lot of like install
Officers who are bald and military people who are bald, so I mean and they're not
The Internet has created a lot of install shit, and it gives in cells and outlet instead of like
Going and getting some pussy. They just have an outlet to be an instill 24-7
Like Brandon Q. Yeah, I mean I love that she immediately just
knows it's Brandon Q. But I mean, like, you know, Crack Rock Chris was bald.
Zayas not bald. Oh, yeah.
I'm going to talk to my mom earlier because I was talking to shoot about crack.
Now, how do you feel that Alex is making a game of Crack Rock Chris at Diddler?
No.
Am I just making that up crack rock Chris is a crackhead who
Asked me this crystal. Will you fuck me and so I can lose my virginity. Is he a weirdo or not?
This is actually hilarious crystal
Okay, thank you. Okay, so crack rock Chris one time. Of course
He was like, I'm so mad at gamble and everything because they were making fun of him being the virgin, right?
He goes crystal fuck me and like that way or just say that you did and so that I can tell people that I lost my virginity
To crystal and I was like, yeah, I was like that's weird
Like and I had to block him after that because it was weird and he only wanted to do that to get back at gamble
And I thought it was weird and I was like, what the fuck
Yeah
Then he would have died not a virgin
Like Tommy low and what was like around me? He was a virgin like I don't get it like that was weird
But he was so like upset with him was like I just want it
There's nobody else that's gonna ever be like crack right Chris. He's our favorite
No, look the the TLDR is like I was his friend
I was cracker Chris's friend for a while. I like them. Yeah, and I tried getting Chris off drugs
I used to send him money to gamble so that he would have something to do and I'm glad he's dead and
He but listen listen
I love that Chris was Chris was crystal. Let me trust me. You don't know how here
Crystal, you were not here for any of this, and if I tell you what happened, you'll think a little bit differently.
No, Crystal. Crystal, let me just forgive me. I don't...
If you're asking about... If you're talking about crack or Chris, give me five minutes to explain it, please.
Okay. Because it's very specific.
Chris was off drugs in my server, and then Chris asked Brooklyn.
Remember Brooklyn? Yeah.
Chris asked Brooklyn to send him Xanax and she did and then Chris got wasted and started crashing out on
Everyone and like threatening everyone in the server and then it became clear that Brooklyn was the one who did it
So we banned her for like encouraging his relapse and then Chris eventually
He was banned and then tried telling everybody that I was a pedophile the same way that Brandon does. Yeah
Chris called my father every single day. He swatted me
He went into every chat in every community to say whatever he could about how I was me and my dad were sex-trafficking
Pedophiles that were trying to get him killed and all sorts of shit
And then the foosie thing happened and then Chris came back and I forgave him because Chris is a junkie and junkies do crazy shit
and I wanted to see him do better.
And then within like two or three weeks of him being back,
Chris started trying to send Xanax to a girl
that I was talking to.
And Chris got banned again.
And then I ended up having sex with a viewer.
And then Chris ended up falling in love with that viewer.
And like, quote, he's dating her for a few months
and then she one night in.
One night she said she was gonna come to my house again, and it literally broke Chris's heart
So he ordered Xanax, but he orders pressed Xanax that usually have fentanyl in them and he died two days later
That's what happened. That's the CLDR of Chris. There's a lot more to that.
We'll try to blame Gamble. We'll try to blame Gamble. Meanwhile, he would go be...
back and forth between Gamble and Wilbur all the time.
That's deep lore. Deep Crack Rock Chris lore.
And also relevant, Brandon Q likes to say,
Gamble raped Steph. That's the girl that I had sex with twice.
That Crack Rock Chris was obsessed with. Crack Rock Chris tried to get her to say
that I raped her and she multiple times on calls with everyone said,
And Brandon Q and Chris both say say that game will raped you tell every tell everybody that game will raped you
And that's where the whole gamble rape stuff thing comes from is from crack rock
Chris and Brandon Q being obsessed with some random girl that I didn't date that I fucked twice
That's it
Not done that you know a gamble I think it I think it's still all your fault according to those two
I think it's all your fault
It's a matter of perspective, I guess.
I mean, I killed him, and I killed Aaron.
I know.
It's all your fault, Gamble.
Just blame Gamble.
That's the biggest, that's the easiest cop out.
You know, my life went to Gamble's fault.
I was just trying to get me out to prayer.
Gamble, why did you tear my life apart?
What's wrong with you?
It's your fault.
Damn, Chris.
They're like almost the master master mastermind behind everything according to crazy Alex mayors
Chris delaying your fucking asshole is bigger than a helipad
If we could bring my microphone, so you quit talking about my ass
Even after all of that I would rather have Chris back instead of fucking brain and Q
No doubt in my mind no doubt no doubt no doubt
A lot more easily contained, I guess I didn't know you had just I don't know how you put it
Q I
Thought you and Chris were like you're addressing me boys
Yeah
No, because whenever I went on fucking Tommy James's panel one day
He started calling me a diddler out of nowhere ever since then it's been fuck
You know what I did I celebrated and I drank a lot of beers
Yeah, why are we I celebrated I celebrated when cracker Chris died. I'm sorry
That's his fault man. I mean we made a shirt
That's why earlier that's why earlier
In your chat when I said, oh, it's funny how the person who called everybody a diddler turned out to be a diddler
And then I said I was talking about crack rock Chris. That's what I was talking about
He went on panels calling everybody it did love then had some suspect shit happened to him then he passed away like a month later
You know, so you know days later. Oh, I don't know
Well within this the the last time I talked to Chris Chris died 48 hours later
That's why a lot of people say that it's my fault because the last time anybody saw him on alive was a brutal like five hour live
Where he was getting like
Whoa, it was really bad.
Yeah.
Well, he would have did the joke on our list.
He wouldn't have done that.
He would have done that.
I thought he was like gonna put it to his head and his mom out of like no
No, what that's what I'm saying. You're making this up
Is that is that from a clip that you've seen of him in his room playing with a gun shooting?
Yeah, okay, so you saw a clip and you're now like making up a whole story around it that has nothing to do with it
That's Chris just really high on crack shooting an airsoft gun and when his mom comes any points that at her
It's just a clip of him being retarded.
Yeah, I didn't know if it was to himself or his mom.
It was like one of the others.
That's just a meme clip of him.
I never watched the clip.
I just saw the meme, and I thought it was weird.
Jesus Christ.
No, I actually tried to get Chris off the hook.
Imagine if my name was fucking Crack Rock Q.
I did DXM with Chris, but that's something that people take to get off drugs actually
And he didn't do anything else while he was doing that. So it's a shame
When's the last time you when's the last time you was the last time you did the rubies? Oh
I mean like root dude, I don't know a long time ago
Like what like before or after COVID?
No, I mean after Kobe, not like that.
Oh, it's slow dancer and fiancé.
No, no, I mean before after like...
Wait, slow dancer, fiancé?
Before after like the Kobe...
No, 2023 maybe.
It's still after, dude. Like 20, 25, like a year or two ago.
Not that long ago.
Wait, wait, Gamble, is slow dance your fiancé?
Yeah.
No, it's a Joji song.
I didn't know that until I saw this. I love you, baby.
Mm-hmm. Uh-huh. That's cute. Shut up, Blobfish.
Yeah, I remember it was like three four years ago was too long ago to really remember
Oh, I love you too game of fiance slow dance
So this whole time. I've been like like liking slow dance and had no idea though as your fiance
Yeah, well, there you go even better. Yeah, cuz she's so nice to not be bald
Right I got plenty of hair. I
Wish I knew what that was like. My dad has more hair than brain in QQ has great hair, too
Mm-hmm. No, I'm going bald. I'm going bald. There's nothing wrong with being bald
Who has hair on my level? He's just his environment is not as kept up
I don't know the fuck you calling me fucking greasy shine the cleanest streamer that exists
Everybody
No, it's because I can't wash my hair every day because then it starts to like fuck up it starts
Then I start to get like a dry scalp. So I have to do it like every three days
That's the sweet spot for me is like three four and then
Yeah, because if you do it every every day, then you just dry the shit out of your follicles
But if you do it like too late, then you just live like a greasy bastard
You know what sometimes I like the grease because it like keeps my hair down like when I have it up
It's like a natural fucking
for the cable next on IRL news time I
Literally just really high because are you
Gable are you like Italian at all you have any Italian in you?
Yeah, what are you but what is your heritage my grant? Well, my dad's side is
His my dad's mother
was born in Spain and my dad's grandmother was born in Naples and
Yeah, the rest are all
So you're like half big, half guinea, oh my god.
And then my mom's night is all British.
You could trace her just through American all the way back to British with some natives
being, I guess they were inclusive or they were rapists, either one, but it seemed like
they were legal marriages.
Okay, agreed what Anita said.
Uh, sex trafficking, racist, wingers,
pepeteering, chrysler for the cabal, and next on Ira.
Yeah, I know, right? Me and my fiance are both saying we love you.
Now she's going to say we're a new thrupple,
and that we're enticing you with our thrupple
so that you'll do what we want.
Like our little sex slave for two years. I didn't even talk to gamble one time
I was like hi crystal. Oh, she's still mad at the miscarriage thing and whatever
But the thing is is for two years. I honestly
I didn't talk to Gammels, I'm not sure how he's manipulating me.
Man, like I barely been back.
I just have so much power that I could just poof and then control everything all of you
guys say and do.
It's not just-
It's all self-awareness.
It's not that I'm just picking a really low common denominator of not appreciating pedophile
rapey people.
He isn't scaredy.
It's not that.
I saw that you let's just be honest with that with rejection
I just want to make this clear too. I have never
Once thought oh boy. Do I want to stream on you?
Joy my kick streams where?
A very different group of people watch and I do completely different things and nobody ever mentions anything about this at all.
Yeah, I may go back to Tiktok because...
I didn't even say anything. I feel upset.
I've been on kick. Dude, it's in my thing. I put it into my game.
I know. I hit the follow button. You didn't even acknowledge me. It's disgusting.
When?
I followed you last night.
Yesterday.
I made a whiff out.
When what?
Have a look at your move. Can you can you go look at your most recent?
Okay, I bet you I bet you'll see my name in there you didn't say nothing. Thank you slow dance. You're the only disgusting
No, what are who are you? Who are you? You're not you're not you'll know if you look at your most recent followers
You're you're not John. Don't give a fuck. Oh wait, are you? No
Yeah, you're not at or you're not at a Royal Andy. You're not Terry Davis. Those are the last ones that I'm see
Hey, you didn't get my subscription. Yeah, you're looking at
Are you looking at kick
Last night I even downloaded the kick live app so I was like somebody may have run over you. That's my bad
What about DX Temecula chapter?
What is it?
You might find that one or you could find the one that says Q45 there's a couple of them
I have a bunch of accounts on cake. What is fucking going on?
Okay, we were in here gonna be a huge target for Brandy Q, but game
God I mean if she wants to you give us a but I don't think she wants one and yeah
There's a reason why I wasn't like hey, that's my fiance in the chat because it's better. It's not right
All right, hold on. I gotta rejoin. I can't hear because Tommy left
A fish I
Don't know if I should go get another beer if I should show
This is like one of those plans for like just don't have to make it
Oh, no, I'm not gonna do anything crazy if I was gonna do that. I would have already done it
I had two four locos already. Oh, this I'm crazy
Alex has this like weird angle
She's so mad and that she wants me and gamble to not talk for whatever reason
But then again, she's caught contradicting herself saying like gamble is a PDF. No, he's not no
He's supposed to be an AF. No, I don't like these blacks
Oh my gosh, Q.
Do you have but I'm just saying George Wallace amount of emotional damage that me and Gamble have done by not doing anything
Is the hysterical part?
That's why people like watching the crash out because she disabled her whole chat
But it's mad and she can't be mad at me that viewers came here when she had
Brandy Q on her stream. She didn't give a fuck about Gamble's feelings
She had like a day and a half to acknowledge his feelings and she didn't that was her fault
So now she's such a mean person, but the reason why I like to listen to her is because I know she's a liar, right?
She's not gonna get the reaction out of me. She looks crazy as fuck. I'm she's exposing herself
I don't even have to do anything because I have to put her on my tv and people can hear it
You just have to sit here and be Korean just like brain and kid when he restrain well wait gamble
I'm gonna go do some I'm gonna do some IRL you wanna see some hookers
No, yes
11 San Bernardino right on the blade. I just got a fucking I'm gonna take a piss let my phone charge for a second
And we're gonna go get some beer and some hocus and and also cute
I have some people that came in. I was dreaming with them last night. We were dancing and everything. It was hilarious
So Q will rather hang out with gamble chicken Andy, but not me
See, I told you, he hasn't given me a closet.
Hey, Crystal, why don't you shut your fucking mouth up?
Brandon was in Alex's chat saying that he thinks that you want him, Crystal.
What?
Brandon was in Alex's chat saying that you want him, that you're obsessing over him,
like Aaron Carter, and that you want him.
That's gross.
He's obsessing over me.
Yeah, that's what it seems like.
But here we go now you get to experience what I've experienced you get to experience the guy blame you for shit that he's doing
No, she wants me James. I
Can call you that my real name is James
I know that's my real name nice
I'm gonna call him Jimmy
Yeah, oh my god, that's what my family calls me
I'm gonna call you Willie. I'm gonna call you Willie
To you have the same number as my actual brother so it makes sense what number
My brother you have the same number you talking about woman
Crystal you outlasted all of these streams
Like sail went live Alex went live and Brandon went live and you're still queen crypto always wins
Man, I just wanted to sing for a bit. I was like, this is too much like my brain
Absorb anything still seeing I did these blacks don't have the stamina. That's why Michael Phelps is the greatest swimmer
I
Really
So they become hey, you tell me it's not true
No, I don't know what to say at this point anything I say makes Q mad
No, everything I say makes you mad crystal dork
Okay, okay
That's why you were like mad at me for singing like turn that's why you were making fun of me earlier for being an orphan
No, I didn't you made that up. I got my phone up for being
You were an orphan and you were born from orphans. I never Wow
You're such a terrible. Can you even hear me?
Why would crystal even say something like that?
Okay, so are you there are you there? I'm here. Can you hear me? Yes or no? Hello?
Hello, can you not hear me? Can anybody hear me? I don't know what the hell is going on with her
Can anybody can anybody hear me?
No, we can't hear you don't lie
Are you always lying?
Giant shrimp, can you hear me? Oh, yeah, Q. You're a liar. I
Was literally talking back to you you idiot
Why are you all getting now that now it's just me and you Crystal well gamble left so it's just me and you baby girl
Oh my god, you really did call me babe earlier. Like he said what I thought I am your soldiers
Oh my god, this is gonna go so bad when Alex hears that
Like some young got 20 and she's 37 like thanks. Thanks for that. Thank you. Thanks
Congratulations, you just know is that she never was able to have anybody fuck her or marry her. That's what's her problem
I mean, you'll probably be in that same predicament too, but I doubt you'll be upset about it. I'm taken
You're not yeah, but you're you're past the age. You can't have a kid anymore with hookers on the street. I
Know I love my hookers part of my community and then you go and that's my big sister on the street
And then there's a part of my community. What's wrong with that?
We I thought we were sticking to the thing that we actually protect hookers around here
I thought we were just sticking to the part that I'm your younger brother or nothing more than that so why would you
I thought you were a fucking, I thought you were a person
Are you really referring to me as Bita right now Q? You really do deserve a door in your face
Twinging doors. Do you need a shoulder to cry on?
Not from you
You need a shoulder to cry on. Can I sing you a song?
Need a little patience
I've been walking streets tonight just trying to keep it right
So you can sing but I can't sing, right?
Don't like being stuck on the ground
You know I don't like being stuck on the ground
But I need you
All this time
You was taking her for granted
See if there's more
Cue
What you little whore?
Shut up
So no
Yeah
Go to your room. Hey, if you don't get drunk and sing fucking patients by guns and roses
I don't want to talk to you. Well, I was singing good show and you wouldn't sing it with me
And you wouldn't even sing blink 182 with me. I don't know that dorky-ass shit. I'm listening
I was singing guns and I forgot you're nine years younger than me. So you wouldn't Jesus Christ
No, I actually I listen to music. That's before a year fucking. Oh, you were ever even in your daddy's ball back
Don't bring up my dad into this
No, I'm not I'm just I was bringing up his ball sack. Why bringing up that's gross because that's where you came from
No, but no boss. No, what you're what you came from daddy's ball sack true or false
Will you stop burnt saying that that's weird
Daddy's ball sack too. It's off cue. I really am I'm gonna throw up. I was the fastest swimmer
Did you know that they have like
I was like that. I was like the milk
It's like the Olympic sperm race or whatever
See now you're getting really gross. No, that's really a thing
No, it's really a thing
Cute it's a thing Google it. Don't you don't you cue me?
I got came from you ever you have a really dirty mind. I was in my mother's womb not my
I'm like nobody can carry a baby in a ball sack you weirdo
No, there really is a thing of like yeah, I carry I I'm probably carrying a million babies in my ballsack right now
Are you kidding me? You know, do you understand how sperm works you understand how male anatomy works?
All of the sperm that populates the world is kept inside of every male's nutsack right now
Huh, I don't want to know that you're just an incubator
What?
Yeah, you're right. Do you need your you're an incubator?
You're an incubator deal with it
You're kind of being weird
How am I being weird you're being weird you need a pacifier to soothe right?
He didn't stop running your cocksucker go grab your binky. I
Don't have any more beard go grab your binky the self-sooth. I
Don't know what's wrong with him y'all tonight. He's on one
He was funny the other night, but tonight. I don't know
Then he's trying to be weird. Oh
That's you
No, that's you that's annoyed of you
You're always mean to me every time I join the panel you never have any grace towards me you have grace towards everyone else
It's okay. I see how you operate crystal. I say how you fucking operate
Wow crummy a river. I
like
Can't stand you
Little brother would say
I can't stand you because you won't let me come into your room. I can't stand you
That's when I hit you with the door
But you actually do love me so it's fine whatever he says
He only says little things because he wants me
was always so far this has been twice tonight babe baby girl like what what
route are we going I don't need a match with anyone I can do that by myself
I want to have war games with you, but you want to have war games with other people like actual like
Like like doing like go-kart racing and see who wins because I bet you I'd win and then also like
Bowling to see who wins. I would win play pool. I'd win
Any like we can go kayaking and I'd win the kayaking race. Okay, maybe you'll win that one actually but whatever
Like laser tag. I don't know
Don't know why every time you have that photo when you use that photo it just makes me like feel like I have to be nice to you
It sucks
You don't have to be nice man never asked you to
No, I never came online pretending to be a good guy
But you seem so sad there. So I feel like if I'm like being mean like you're like, no
It's more like, you know, it's more like I'm looking at the camera like why the fuck you taking a picture of me
It's more like a you know, it's like a
You look so sad it's kind of like a it's like a it's like a precursor to how I am in real life as an adult
So should I put a photo that's why I love that picture so much because I'm looking at the camera like what the fuck are you looking at?
That's why I love that picture I
Should change my picture to when I was a little kid around that age. I was cute. No, don't copy me chicken cakes already did that
Why?
Everybody everybody copy me when I did that
So then I had to put face tattoos on
Believe that me and you are like brother and sister because we had no I'm no no you're like ten years older than me woman
as a cute kid
Yeah, I mean everybody who is moon face. That's probably cute as a kid
You'll me show you
No, I don't want to see pictures of you as a kid
Nobody does it's probably better that you don't show anything
Especially with the war that's brewing
How do you feel about the crystal burst starting with a cue that people are shipping? I
Feel like I'm really good-looking and I'm really tall and I'm happy with the size of my cock. I
Don't want to hear about that. Why do you want like I'm just letting you know you asked me how I felt
That's all I feel chicken my cat is really annoyed by you
Don't give a fuck
Yeah, I'll adopt that cat
What is your deal
What's your deal I
Don't have a deal
And stop doing so much Adderall. Maybe you'll stop talking so much
Don't take Adderall. Thank you very much. They're not
They're not I'll find out. Oh
Like now you're like my medicine, please
No, I don't but whatever
I'm your doctor
You're so weird
So weird a background
I want to put a galaxy
I
Now that's a sex symbol right there. Oh my gosh, you think everything is you know who that is
What?
I'm on profile picture. What isn't that? Why does that look like?
No, I don't know who that is
That's mog why that's what I thought but I didn't want to be wrong. I didn't want to say his name
Why are you doing that now? He's gonna come after me look what you know? He doesn't he's not
He will be like he's a weirdo bullshit. Yeah, you know what the funniest part is I live
I lived I live to I live two blocks away from him and he never did nothing
I live two blocks away from him in Pittsburgh. We're from the same city
I found out that me and him lived two blocks away from each other, and he never did anything.
That dude's scared as fuck.
No, it was in Pennsylvania, and you live in California, make that, make sure-
No, no, no, I'm saying where I'm from.
Like, where I was when I first started streaming for the first three years of me streaming.
We lived one or two blocks away from each other, and he never did anything.
That guy is such a bitch.
Like, he's such a little pussy.
You think he's gonna do anything to you and fucking Oklahoma? That's Mogwai. He's a cornball
I'm not afraid of Mogwai. Like I hope not. I used to he's I hope not Instagram lives all the time you ding dong
He's like a ghost these days. He doesn't even exist
Yes, he does he was in my chat the other day you ding dong
No, but people people go and create you can't you can't
Can't be sure these days
It's like damn near impossible
There's something wrong with you
No, there's something wrong with you crystalline
No, you know
Crystal fish
Did you eat dinner? Hi? How are you? How is your day going? What'd you say to me woman?
Hey, you know what we should do? Why are you telling me to shut up? That's not nice
We should go we
Chilli cheese Fritos
Why do you want chili cheese?
Wait, that's my younger brother and I must protect him at all costs. Crystal. Can you stop talking for a second? Please listen?
Why do you want chili cheese Fritos?
Oh my
You had enough money to buy the fucking meth that you're smoking then why didn't you not buy the chili cheese prudos?
Stop gaslighting her ding dong. Hey crystal. I did not smoke you did I hit you with I'm not gaslighting her
You asked me a question, right? I
Didn't gaslight her she called me over here
You're allowing her to be on me how rude
No, she she didn't say anything about you
Yes, she did
What's wrong with crystal?
That's my brother are you the candy man?
No, but there's no Washington. No, that's not Denzel Washington was not the candy man. No, that's false
You never seen the movie then
Denzel Washington is still alive
My
Well, this is who Q talks to when he's bored
Why do you pay yourself in situations like that, I'm gonna store a woman be quiet I
Want to say hi to the manager touch your horn mouth up, please
Is this the Family Dollar Manager?
I know women, it's very hard for women to stop talking, but please.
Are you at the Family Dollar?
Like, maybe now is the time when you can exercise that.
Yeah, I'm at the Family Dollar.
Hi, Family Dollar Manager.
Who made you famous?
On my street.
Don't understand Spanish
Hola, hola
She's speaking Farsi. Oh, I don't know that language either
Yeah, I have to be the translate
Shut up
Thank you. Gracias
How's it going pretty good
Oh god, should we go again?
This is why Q is estranged from him
What happened to me?
So Q, does your mom like, did she still, did she pass or no?
It goes to my parents for a day, for a long time.
That's sad.
Oh, well, I got done crying about it like, you know, a couple of years ago
Actually, it's more the people online that talk about it more than I even think about it
Like I wouldn't even think about it that much if it wasn't for people online that constantly spam the chat talking about my dead mommy and my dead daddy
I don't sit around crying about it these people try to sit around and trigger me about it is what it is though
I'm sorry
You don't have to be sorry
I'm not gonna say I don't care, but I'm just it's just not like it's been so long now
I mean my mom died in 2016 and my dad died in like 2013. So it's been a long ass time
It's not like anything that just happened recently were you the only child
So my dad had three kids
Um, and my mom only had one kid, so I'm one of my I have two half mothers or two one half brother and one half sister
I hate fucking dogs. They never
Don't I really don't like dogs
I'm sorry that this is like a controversial unpopular opinion. I really don't like dogs
Sometimes they just they'd never shut the fuck up or just annoying as fuck
I don't like dogs, I don't like them.
Dilo, come here.
Shiai, Shiailo!
Why are you sleeping on the dresser?
He wants to sleep on the dresser, it's weird.
Dilo, come here, come to the bed where it's more comfy.
Hi
Alex is so lurking and there's no hookers off. They must I think they've been doing like a clean up recently because I've seen a lot less hookers
I used to see like millions of them fuck like like maybe at least ten down every street and now it's just like a ghost town
They must have the cops must be doing something cute. I'm only my stream. Can you like take over my stream for a little bit?
You already know I'm gonna go chat and Kate's for a little bit. Okay. Oh
Are you gonna be fine by yourself
I'll be great by myself
I'll probably sitting here to more people than you are talking over there
Well, I just want to go show my love and support real fast. Give me like 10 minutes. You should go show your asshole
I can tell Kate that she's fake because she used to let me in there a couple weeks ago
and I was the same amount of racist that I was then that I am now.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Has Q ever spent time alone with a lady of the night? Never.
That's one of the few degenerate things that I probably haven't done in my life is how to hook her.
Because it's like I've just never... Why would I pay for sex? Like I just can't... I've never been that desperate. You know what I mean?
Like I'm sure it's possible for a lot of people depending or regardless of how you look even if you're a good-looking dude
But I've never been at that point where I was like so desperate to where I felt like I needed to go buy a hooker
and
There I know don't get me wrong like when I'm walking, you know
Going getting beers going to 7-eleven. There are some hookers on the blade, and I'm like damn life
You're gorgeous, you know what I mean like fuck if I was gonna buy a hooker
Probably look like you
But I can't I could never bring myself to pay money for sex cuz I already know after I nut
I'm gonna feel like such a fucking idiot. I
Just paid like what 250 something dollars
For some pussy and I'm not even an ugly-ass nigga too like I could get pussy on my own
So, like, that makes me feel even worse about it.
The fact that I'm not an ugly-ass nigga, the fact that I don't look like Sam-Man.
Because if I was ugly, I'd be like, you know what, at least it's better to pay for it than to never experience it at all.
Oh, shit.
I
Now Q is no one to yell at I can yell at you
That's okay, so my phone's about to die actually
It's the oldest profession in the world.
I don't know if it's the oldest profession in the world.
I think maybe like being a construction worker
is the oldest profession in the world
because where were the women having sex at
if it wasn't for men to build the teepees?
I remember my first girlfriend,
she was talking all that feminist shit one day.
We were in downtown Pittsburgh
And I said, you see all these skyscrapers and all this concrete and all this structure you can thank men for that because I guarantee it wasn't a fucking gang of women that built that shit.
You thank the men for building, the men will build the world and we will destroy the world too.
We're responsible for building it and we will destroy it eventually.
Whether it be 50 years from now 10 years from now
150 years from now
eventually
The men that the same men that built the world
Their ancestors
Will fuck or their ancestors ride whatever the fuck
Will destroy it
We have to play some death metal on this bitch. Where's my other stuff?
Crystal's being an ass. We have to play some death metal.
I don't want the Game Boy. I want my other phone. Dick's head.
I don't mean you know where that shit's at.
Is that Alex in your PFP?
Yes.
All right, I'm about to get out of here.
I'm not going to...
846 she it's about that time chicken wing
bang bang
Q you
Accident out what the hell?
Q you were supposed to hold down the fort and you left the fort what is wrong with you this phone probably died
How rude he's coming back
But I have to be here to allow him back because he went to family dollar, which means his phone probably died
Which means by the time he gets home when he puts on the charger, he'll be coming back up. So it's okay
I came back to the people. It's fine
unless
What
Let's just not say a word
Oh, he's watching. Hold on.
He really ditched y'all
Well, I'm back
He fell that his one job
Q
Excuse me bless me bless me Q
Man, how's this guy gonna ditch my string?
Thank you, that was a loud sneeze my goodness
He really left me
Q if you don't hurry up your butt hear it within two minutes, I'm ending my string
Okay, I'm sorry called you my retarded brother
Is clumsy live if clumsy is live that's probably where he went
What exactly did he say
I'll cue his back
I see the numbers kind of going up nope it went down
Q
Stone probably died give it a few minutes
But he said he was gonna come back when I came back
Can someone at him
What is this YouTube channel I don't know it
He held the four down before.
Oh, okay, hold on.
I see a lot of clips of him.
Well
Q I'm ending my stream
I'm in my stream y'all hope everyone has a great night. Love y'all. Bye
He ain't here I
Rather go over to Kate's anyways. All right, I'll be on Kate's chat
Where did he go? He had one job and he fell to now I want to yell at him
Not rude
What's his Instagram?
What is Q's Instagram? Does anybody know his Instagram?
Hold on
Alright, well good night everyone. I can't believe Q ditched every- wait, no, I think he's coming back. The numbers went up again
Usually when the numbers start going back up that means Q's
coming back
Q, Q, Q fine, whatever
Q, you have five minutes
Okay, everyone. Let's go to cage chat. Bye